Advertise your product or brand here contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-
To me, being a guidance counselor, it's kind of like being
Para mí, ser orientadora es como ser
a teacher of emotions.
profesora de emociones.
You know, you help these kids figure out what they're feeling and...
Ayudas al alumnado a entender lo que sienten
show them how to express it in a healthy way, you know?
y les enseñas a expresarlo de forma sana.
That was beautifully put.
Qué bien suena eso.
Well, you know, we have been looking at more seasoned candidates, but...
Bueno, hemos estado buscando personal más veterano, pero...
I, for one, think we could use someone with a little pep in her step.
yo creo que es buena idea tener a alguien más energético.
I'm so happy my lack of experience didn't dissuade you.
Me alegro de que mi falta de experiencia no sea un problema.
I actually think it's a selling point.
Es un punto a favor.
You know? I'm not, like, rigid.
No soy tan... estricta.
I'm not bogged down by that whole
No me echa para atrás lo de: "Así es como siempre se ha hecho".
Yes, this is a Catholic school,
Sí, es una escuela católica,
but even religions have to adapt with the times.
pero las religiones tienen que adaptarse.
Adapt how?
¿Cómo?
Well, take sex ed, right?
Con educación sexual.
You can teach abstinence all you want, but kids are gonna have sex.
Pueden hablarles de abstinencia pero tendrán relaciones.
They are kids.
Son jóvenes.
I mean, don't get me wrong. I'm pro-marriage.
Pero estoy a favor del matrimonio.
It's one of the reasons my ex and I broke up.
Por eso rompimos mi ex y yo.
I will tell you about Eric one day, and you will flip the fuck out
Cuando le hable de Eric se va a quedar flipando...
because that man is a liar.
porque no podía ser más mentiroso.
Okay, well, why don't we just do a scenario here?
Vale, imaginemos una cosa.
Let's say a student comes to you
Digamos que una alumna
to tell you that her boyfriend is pressuring her to get physical.
le dice que su novio la está presionando para hacerlo.
First of all, fuck that guy. You know, I would shut that down.
En primer lugar, que le den a ese chaval. Le diría que lo dejara.
Yeah, I would use it as an opportunity to teach her
Sería una oportunidad para enseñarle que no necesita un chico para satisfacerse.
She can fulfill herself.
Puede hacerlo sola.
- Spiritually. - Oh, no. Physically.
- Espiritualmente. - No. Físicamente.
Phys...
Física...
- Masturbating. - Well...
- Masturbándose. - Bueno...
I mean, I'm not gonna be hands-on about it.
No sería una clase práctica.
- Can you imagine? - Thank God.
¿Se lo imagina?
I just want her to know she has options.
Que sepa que tiene opciones.
Maybe it's a shower nozzle or an owl... figurine.
Quizá sea un grifo o una figura de búho.
My first boyfriend was a teddy bear.
Mi primer novio fue un oso de peluche.
God, I loved to masturbate.
Dios, me encantaba masturbarme.
Great. Okay, then.
Genial. Vale.
Yes, I still do.
Lo sigo haciendo.
Oh, yeah, it does.
¿Cómo que no?
You are fucking nuts.
Estás como una puta cabra.
Who rambles on to a nun about sex?
¿Quién habla de sexo con una monja?
I mean, it's like, I knew I shouldn't go there,
Sabía que no debía ir allí,
but in the moment I was like, I should go there.
pero luego decidí ir.
There's the things that you say when you have the job,
Se dicen unas cosas cuando tienes trabajo
and things that you say when you want the job.
y otras cuando lo quieres.
I don't know what you want me to tell you.
No sé qué quieres que te diga.
I fucking did it. It happened.
Lo hice. Pasó.
Oh, that's classic Aunt Wesley.
Típico de la tía Wesley.
You know what? Sweetie, I think it all worked out in the end.
Creo que al final todo salió bien.
You're too forward-thinking for that place.
Eres demasiado progre.
They're so-so uptight.
Ahí son muy estirados.
- I need a job. - Uh-mm.
Necesito un trabajo.
Everyone in my master's program has one.
Mis compañeras del máster trabajan.
- That girl who ate her hair for two years? - Ugh.
Aquella chica que se comía el pelo
She has a job and a boyfriend.
tiene trabajo y novio.
- Sweetie,
Cariño...
don't compare yourself to other people. It's a loser's game.
No te compares. Nunca sale bien.
I thought by the time I was 30,
Pensé que a los 30 años
I'd be married with, like, this dope career and a couple kids.
estaría casada, con una carrera y tendría un par de hijos.
Ugh! Being married is not the answer.
Casarse no es la respuesta.
Dave cheated on me,
Dave me engañó,
so you never know how that's gonna go.
nunca sabes cómo saldrá.
I'm not even going on Instagram anymore,
Ya no entro a Instagram,
because I cannot see another pregnant belly
porque no quiero ver otra barriga con "nueve meses" escrito en ella.
But I'm so happy for everyone else.
Pero me alegro por los demás.
Sorry I called you a bitch when you told me you were pregnant.
Perdona por haberte insultado.
Oh, Kevin's just depressed lately.
Últimamente está deprimido.
Oh, really? Did he find out he looks like Hitler?
¿Ha descubierto que se parece a Hitler?
Kevin does not look like Hitler.
No se parece a Hitler.
He really does.
Bastante.
No, Kevin, you can't go outside. You're an indoor cat.
No, no puedes salir. Eres un gato de interior.
I don't know what he's trying to prove.
No sé qué quiere demostrar.
- Hi, sweetie. - Hi.
Hola, cariño.
- Welcome home. Cheese plate. - What's up ladies?
- Bienvenido. ¿Queso? - ¿Qué tal?
Hey, sorry about the job, Wes.
Siento lo del trabajo, Wes.
- Kaylie told me you didn't get it. - Thanks, man.
- Ya sé que no te lo dieron. - Gracias.
Yeah, I mean, the archaic institution of organized religion
Sí, la arcaica institución de la religión
is no place for our friend Wes here.
no es lugar para nuestra amiga Wes.
See? Tad gets it.
Eso es.
Wes, why haven't you called Tad's friend Sean yet?
¿Has llamado al amigo de Tad?
- Yeah. - I got a lot of guys in the mix right now.
- Sí. - Hablo con varios chicos.
Some of them are ghosting me,
Algunos me ignoran,
which means they have my undivided attention.
o sea que tienen toda mi atención.
You know what? Why don't you just chill on the guys
Oye, ¿por qué no dejas lo de buscar pareja
until you find a job, you know? One crisis at a time.
hasta que encuentres trabajo? Paso a paso.
Okay, Brooke.
Vale, Brooke.
Yeah, I'll just casually take a year off of dating
Sí, estaré otro año soltera
while my ovaries rust and grow barnacles.
mientras mis ovarios se oxidan.
Oh, Wes, there's always a silver lining.
Hay que ver el lado positivo.
Even on corroded ovaries.
Incluso en ovarios corroídos.
Oh, my God. What was that?
¿Qué ha sido eso?
Well, at least you don't have a job to drive to.
Al menos no tienes que trabajar.
Wesley, doll, it's Mom.
Wesley, cielo, soy mamá.
I haven't heard from you in a few days, and you know how I worry. I start...
Hace días que no sé de ti y sabes cómo me preocupo. Empiezo...
Hey, Wesley, this is Patty.
Wesley, soy Patty.
You babysat the boys last week,
Cuidaste de mis niños
and I noticed some of the food has been missing from my fridge.
y noté que faltaba algo de comida en la nevera.
And I don't mean to accuse you of anything,
No quiero acusarte de nada,
but it's a little strange,
pero es un poco raro.
so I wondered if you knew...
Me preguntaba si sabías...
Hey, Wes. It's Eric.
Hola, Wes. Soy Eric.
- Been a while, huh? - Like six months.
Cuánto tiempo, ¿eh? Como seis meses.
Kinda awkward to do this on voicemail, but guess what?
Es incómodo por el buzón de voz, pero ¿sabes qué?
I got engaged!
Me voy a casar.
Crazy, right? I know.
Qué locura, ¿no? Lo sé.
I guess I'm the marrying kind after all.
Al final soy de los que se casan.
So, I wanted to give you a heads-up.
Quería avisarte.
My fiancée, Lauren, went to Penn with an editor at Brides magazine.
Mi prometida, Lauren, fue a Penn con un editor de la revista Novias.
They did a piece on our engagement.
Publicarán nuestra pedida.
It's nothing. I mean, a tiny paragraph, a few pictures.
No es nada. Quiero decir, un pequeño párrafo, unas fotos.
- It's on page 75 of the May issue. - Sorry.
Página 75 del número de mayo.
Just letting you know so you don't stumble on it by accident.
Solo te avisaba para que no te lo encontraras por accidente.
Okay. Take care.
Vale. Cuídate.
- Buh-bye. - Oh, fuck.
- Adiós. - Joder.
What? Ew!
¿Qué?
Piggyback ride? Gross.
A caballito. Qué cutre.
"Thought I wasn't meant for marriage,
"Creía que no me casaría.
but I guess it was a matter of meeting the right person." Oh.
Solo tenía que conocer a la persona adecuada".
"Whirlwind courtship included travel..."
"De novios viajamos mucho..."
I love to travel. You never fucking traveled with me.
Me encanta viajar. Nunca viajaste conmigo.
My God, she's European?
Madre mía, ¿es europea?
Okay.
Vale.
- Hello? - Hey, Sean? Uh, this is...
- ¿Diga? - Hola, Sean. Soy…
- Wesley, Tad's friend. - Uh, who?
- Wesley, la amiga de Tad. - ¿Quién?
Sorry, I thought he maybe mentioned to you that I'd be calling.
Lo siento, pensé que te habría dicho que te llamaría.
Oh, right, right... Yeah. You're the magician.
Ah, sí. Es verdad. Eres la maga.
No, I was the one that Tad thought you might hit it off with.
No, soy la amiga que te quería presentar Tad...
Know what? We don't need to do this.
No te preocupes.
I think Tad was just throwing crap at a wall.
Tad querría echar una mano y ya.
Nah, I was just messing with you.
No, era broma.
- Most blind dates are crap, though. - Exactly.
- Las citas a ciegas son una mierda. - Sí.
I always feel like, on a blind date, you should have an automatic out.
En una cita a ciegas, deberías tener una salida automática.
You show up, say hi, no chemistry? Just say no. Over.
Apareces, saludas, ¿no hay química? Di que no. Se acabó.
I'm talking to you right now, I literally don't care about you.
Estoy hablando contigo, pero me das igual.
You could get hit by a bus, could care less.
Como si te atropellan.
I know. Exactly.
Eso es. Exacto.
But look, um, I'm just walking out of a movie right now.
Pues estoy saliendo del cine.
- Okay. - Do you live near Echo Park?
¿Vives cerca de Echo Park?
Maybe we could meet for a drink or...
Podríamos tomar algo…
That sounds great.
Suena genial.
- Thank you so much. - Good night, miss.
- Gracias. - Buenas noches.
Good night.
Buenas noches.
- Are you Sean? - No, I'm not.
- ¿Eres Sean? - No, no soy yo.
- Wesley? - Sean?
- ¿Wesley? - ¿Sean?
- Yes. - Oh, thank God.
- ¿Qué? - Ah, menos mal.
Thought you were that short dude over there. He's adorable,
Creía que eras ese tipo bajito. Nuestros hijos serían bajitos.
Help me.
Ayuda, ayuda.
Yes. Exactly.
Sí. Exacto.
- Hi. - Oh, hi. I took a chance you like white.
Me la he jugado y he elegido blanco.
- Yeah. - Um...
Sí.
- So, how do you know Tad? - "How do I know Tad?"
- ¿De qué conoces a Tad? - Pues...
Let's see. I dated a girl in college that he worked with.
Salí con una chica con la que trabajaba.
- Jessie Harris? - Yeah, I know Jessie.
- ¿Jessie Harris? - La conozco.
- Okay. - Wonder why she didn't try to set us up.
¿Por qué no nos presentó?
That's weird. Yeah, usually,
Qué raro. Sí, por lo general,
when girls get married,
cuando las chicas se casan, comparten su montón de rechazados.
"Reject pile."
"Rechazados".
Ooh, I wish that hot husband of hers was in the reject pile.
Ojalá su marido estuviera en la lista de rechazados.
Have you seen their perfect baby?
¿Has visto que bebé tan perfecto?
I love weddings. Were you at their wedding?
Adoro las bodas. ¿Fuiste?
You know what?
¿Sabes qué?
No.
No.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry. Were you not invited?
Perdona. ¿No estabas invitado?
- That was rude of me. - No, I mean...
- Qué maleducada. - Lo que quiero...
What I mean is... no.
decir es que no.
I'm using my automatic out.
Es mi salida automática.
I'm sorry, what?
Perdona, ¿qué?
"Automatic out," what we spoke about.
Lo que hablamos.
If I wanna leave, if you wanna leave, no harm, no foul?
Si quieres irte, te vas. Sin compromiso.
- I'm using that right now. - Okay, we were riffing.
- Eso digo. - Estábamos charlando.
We were having a fun time. Have you never been on a date?
Lo pasábamos bien. ¿Acaso es tu primera cita?
I mean, come on, now. You were dropping "marriage," "kids," "wedding"
Has dicho "matrimonio", "hijos", y "boda"
in five seconds flat.
en cinco segundos.
Not with us!
¡No era sobre nosotros!
What are you doing?
¿Qué haces?
We were just talking.
Solo estábamos hablando.
Wesley, you seem like a great girl.
Pareces una gran chica.
I'm just...
Es que...
- The timing's not right for me. - Guess what?
- No es buen momento. - Mira.
The timing isn't great for me either, Sean.
Para mí tampoco, Sean.
Wanna know why?
¿Sabes por qué?
'Cause I've had a year from hell, all right?
Porque he tenido un año de mierda, ¿vale?
I've had 17 shitty job interviews.
He tenido 17 entrevistas de trabajo.
Twice as many bad dates.
Malas citas.
Okay, my car was destroyed,
No tengo coche.
I'm on a budget, so I steal food from the kid I babysit,
No tengo dinero, cojo comida al niño que cuido.
and all of my birds died this year.
Y se me mueren todos los pájaros.
And my hair is falling out of my head 'cause I blow it out five times a week,
Se me cae el pelo de la cabeza porque me lo seco 5 veces a la semana,
and despite my best efforts, I'm still treading water,
y a pesar de mis esfuerzos, no avanzo,
sitting here on dates with dudes like you,
sigo teniendo citas con tíos como tú,
wondering what my life is gonna be like.
preguntándome cómo será mi vida.
- Unbelievable. - Excuse me.
- Increíble. - Disculpe.
- Baby... - Come on.
- Cariño... - Vamos.
Ma'am. Do you hear me, ma'am?
Señora. ¿Me oye?
Ma'am, I'm an LA City reserve firefighter,
Señora, soy bombero. Pasaba por aquí y se ha caído.
Cool. Thanks, man. I...
Genial. Gracias....
Ma'am, you're gonna be okay, okay? Don't freak out.
Se pondrá bien, no se asuste.
I feel fine.
Estoy bien.
Hey, there. You okay?
Hola. ¿Estás bien?
Oh, my God. Who are you?
Madre mía. ¿Quién eres?
I'm Jared Sterling.
Soy Jared Sterling.
I saw your purse go flying into oncoming traffic.
He visto tu bolso volar hacia la carretera.
I thought you might need some help.
¿Necesitas ayuda?
Wesley Darya of Belmont Avenue, who wears contacts
Wesley Darya, de Belmont Avenue, que lleva lentillas
and somehow got a nice picture on their license.
y sale bien en la foto de carné.
Oh, my God. Shut up.
Madre mía. Cállate.
You okay? You wanna get up? All right.
¿Estás bien? ¿Te levantas? Vale.
Well, time to go to the hospital. I'm down to take you in my Jetta.
Bueno, hay que ir al hospital. Te llevo en mi coche.
I'm fine. I'll have my friends look out for me.
Tranquilo, ahora vienen mis amigas.
Yeah. Oh, okay.
Bueno...
You know what? I...
¿Sabes qué?
I live just around the corner. If you wanna come over,
Vivo aquí al lado. Si quieres venir
you can call some friends to come pick you up.
y que te venga a buscar alguien.
- I do. - I honestly barely ever kill people.
- Vale. - Casi nunca mato gente.
You're so funny.
Eres muy gracioso.
Great. Still not answering, but I can go home.
Genial. No contestan, pero puedo irme a casa.
You don't need to babysit me.
No tienes que cuidarme.
Oh, no. Don't worry about it. I just got back from China.
No. No te preocupes. Acabo de volver de China.
I'd be up all night. You're doing me a favor.
Estaré despierto toda la noche.
Okay.
Entendido.
Aw, cute kid.
Qué mona.
Oh, yeah. That's my nephew.
Sí. Es mi sobrino.
- Hope my own turn out half as great. - Hmm.
Espero que el mío sea igual.
- Yours in the future? - Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- ¿En el futuro? - Sí.
- So, your name's Wesley. - Uh-mm.
Así que te llamas Wesley.
Beautiful eyes.
Con ojazos.
- Organ donor. - Please don't harvest my kidneys.
- Donante. - No me quites los riñones.
I didn't mean to look at your organs when I said that. It was just natural.
No quería mirarte los órganos al decir eso. Ha surgido así.
Uh, no. I'm a sports agent.
No. Soy agente deportivo.
Okay? We only feed on people's careers.
Nos alimentamos de la carrera de la gente.
I don't know anything about agents,
No sé nada de agentes,
so, I... guess I don't have an opinion.
así que no tengo opinión.
My brain's not really working right now, sorry.
Mi cerebro no funciona, lo siento.
I love that.
Me encanta.
Now I know what my problem is.
Sé cuál es mi problema.
I've been being too...
Soy demasiado...
myself.
yo misma.
Yeah. I discovered the secret to men.
He descubierto el secreto.
Don't speak. Look, I'm just facing the facts.
No hablar. Esto es así.
- My personality is an acquired taste. - Hmm.
Mi personalidad es un gusto adquirido.
I love the way your personality tastes.
Me gusta tu personalidad.
I think this is meant to be.
Creo que esto tenía que pasar.
This is exactly like the book
Eso dice el libro
I'm reading right now for my pregnancy journey.
que leo para el embarazo.
It's written by a Mexican shaman named Ángel de la Paz,
Lo escribió una persona mágica: Ángel de la Paz,
Another shaman?
¿Otro chamán?
You might as well be flushing all of your money down the toilet.
Para eso tira el dinero por el váter.
How much did you spend on the last one?
¿Qué te costó la última vez?
Eleven thousand four hundred and eighty dollars.
Once mil cuatrocientos ochenta dólares.
- Right? - That's a lot of money.
- ¿Verdad? - Es mucho dinero.
Listen, the book says
El libro dice
the universe throws a bunch of darkness your way
que el universo te arroja oscuridad
that you have to suffer through in order to find your true path
para que encuentres tu verdadero camino
so that you can appreciate the good things when they come.
y aprecies las cosas buenas cuando lleguen.
Like Jared.
Como Jared.
Thank God. I'm just so relieved.
Gracias a Dios. Qué alivio.
- I was starting to think I was cursed. - You always think you're cursed.
- Pensaba que estaba maldita. - Como siempre.
What do you actually know about this guy?
¿Qué más sabes de él?
He wants kids. He owns a duvet cover.
Quiere hijos. Tiene una funda nórdica.
He liked me with a slight concussion.
Le gustaba con una pequeña contusión.
- What more do I want? - What does he know about you?
- ¿Qué más quiero? - ¿Qué sabe de ti?
He knows that I'm pretty fucking sexy when I'm not talking so much.
Sabe que soy muy sexy cuando no hablo mucho.
Okay, so you're gonna start off a relationship
¿Vas a empezar una relación
by pretending to be a completely different person?
fingiendo ser otra persona?
Yeah.
Sí.
It's a doughnut-wrapped hot dog.
Es un perrito caliente dentro de un dónut.
I have heard so much about this thing.
He oído hablar mucho de esto.
Two of my least favorite things.
Dos de las cosas que más odio.
Totally. Yeah.
Totalmente. Sí.
Man, am I happy you said that.
Cómo me alegro de que hayas dicho eso.
You are so cute. Can we get this out of here, please?
¡Qué mona! ¿Puede llevarse esto?
- Couple salads? - Just a bowl of lettuce.
- ¿Ensaladas? - Solo un bol de lechuga.
- Go, Wes! Go! - Go!
- ¡Vamos!
- Oh, hey, Jared! - Hey!
- Hola, Jared. - ¡Hola!
I'm so excited you like bubble soccer.
Me encanta que te guste esto.
- My ex hated this stuff. - I'm open!
Mi ex lo odiaba.
She's crazy. This is the best.
Está loca. Esto es lo mejor.
- Oh, my God! My body! - Oh, look out!
- ¡Dios mío! ¡Mi cuerpo! - ¡Cuidado!
Oh, my God. I love your laugh, by the way.
Madre mía. Me encanta tu risa.
I wanted... I have to tell you something,
Quería decirte algo...
and I just... I hope it's not a big deal, okay?
y espero que no sea gran cosa.
- Oh, my God. What's up? - So...
- ¿Qué pasa? - ¿Sabes...
you know that girl I told you about? Lucy?
la chica de la que te hablé? ¿Lucy?
We had to call off the wedding last year. She was pretty nuts.
Cancelamos la boda el año pasado. Estaba bastante loca.
She smashed the windows on my car
Rompió las ventanillas de mi coche
and had my mail forwarded to a PO box so she could keep tabs on me.
y usó un apartado de correos para vigilarme.
And I actually came home to find her wearing my clothes,
Un día llegué a casa y me la encontré en la cama
in my bed, so I had to get the locks changed.
con mi ropa, así que cambié las cerraduras.
A psychopath.
Una psicópata.
- Yeah. Luckily, diagnosed now. - Mm.
Por suerte, diagnosticada.
Thanks for telling me. Sorry it didn't work out.
Gracias por contarlo. Lamento que no saliera bien.
And that's it? No...
¿Y eso es todo? No...
no other follow-up questions? No interrogation?
¿No hay más preguntas? ¿Ni interrogatorio?
People make mistakes, you know? Let's keep the past in the past.
La gente comete errores. No remuevas más el pasado.
I think you may be the perfect girl.
Creo que eres la chica perfecta.
Wait. I'm not rushing things, am I?
Espera. No voy muy rápido, ¿no?
No. What? No. Go faster. Harder.
No. ¿Qué? No. Más rápido. Más fuerte.
Wesley Darya,
Wesley Darya,
will you marry me?
¿te casas conmigo?
Yes.
Sí.
Oh, my God. I'm finally happy.
Madre mía. ¡Por fin soy feliz!
- Oh, my God. We have a pool! - What?
- Dios mío. ¡Tenemos piscina! - ¿Qué?
Nothing. Just had a tickle in my throat. Come here.
Un cosquilleo en la garganta. Sigue.
Oh, my God. Mom, you are tripping out.
Mamá, no seas exagerada.
- I'll make the payment. Yes. - I'm tripping? You're still gambling.
- Ya lo pago yo. - Pero sigues jugando.
I don't have a problem with online gambling anymore.
Ya no tengo problemas con el juego.
I told you I took care of that.
Lo superé.
How are you even paying your bills?
¿Cómo pagarás las facturas?
- I wonder, do you have health insurance... - Hold on.
- ¿Tienes seguro? - Un momento.
Now you need a new car.
Necesitas un coche.
- Wasn't him. - You sound like
- No era él. - Pareces
you're about to be homeless.
una sinhogar.
- Do you wanna know what sucks? - Yes.
- ¿Sabes qué es una mierda? - ¿Qué?
Jared's rejecting me, and he doesn't even know me.
Jared me rechaza y ni siquiera me conoce.
There's still a chance he's dead.
A lo mejor está muerto.
You guys are the best.
Sois las mejores.
You're the best.
Tú eres la mejor.
- You guys are the best. - Sweetie, you're the best.
- Sois las mejores. - No, tú.
- What? - It's not Jared. It's my mom.
- ¿Qué? - No es Jared. Es mi madre.
Mom. Fucking stop blowing my line up, man.
Mamá. Joder, deja de llamarme.
You know what? I really think I need to lay down the law.
¿Sabéis qué? Creo que tengo que decirle lo que pienso.
- Yes. - I need to talk my shit to him.
- Sí. - Tengo que hablar con él.
- You know what I'm gonna do?
- ¿Sabéis qué voy a hacer?
- What? - I'm gonna do a e-mail.
- ¿Qué? - Voy a enviarle un correo.
- Do an e-mail. - Yeah, do an e-mail.
- Escribe un correo. - Sí, un correo.
Let's do it. Let's fucking rip it up.
Hagámoslo. Sí, joder.
"In case you're wondering, I'm doing great."
"Por si te lo preguntas, me va genial".
Yeah, you are.
Sí.
"Except for the fact that, five days ago, your penis entered my vagina,
"Excepto por el hecho de que hace 5 días tu pene entró en mi vagina
and I haven't heard from you since.
y no he vuelto a saber de ti.
Does this have to do with the fact that your dead dad
¿Tiene que ver con el hecho de que tu padre muerto
never gave you enough love when you were little?
nunca te diera suficiente amor de pequeño?
Oh, my God. Is that true?
Vaya. ¿Es eso cierto?
Yeah, it's so sad, right?
Sí, qué triste, ¿no?
"May you get drunk and get a dumb unicorn tattoo."
"Ojalá te emborraches y te hagas un tatuaje de unicornio".
"Suck on this, bitch."
"¡Chúpate esa, capullo!"
"Here's a little treat for the woman you're going to torture next.
"Aquí un regalo para la mujer que vas a torturar.
Your dick is bad.
Tu polla es una mierda.
It's legit thin."
Es muy fina".
Eggplant emoji...
Emoji de berenjena.
"Please stop hashtagging all of your Instagrams '#photography.'
"Deja de escribir '#fotografía' en todas las fotos de Instagram.
- Loser. - Everything on Instagram's a photograph.
- Pringado. - Todo en Instagram son fotografías.
Try '#thin dick.'"
Prueba con '#pollafina'.
You suck at Instagram. Why don't you close up shop, dick?
Se te da mal Instagram. ¿Por qué no lo dejas?
- "There's an art to going down on a girl." - Whoo! Yes!
- "El arte de complacer a una chica". - ¡Sí!
- "Do not start the game... - Fucking murder him.
- "No empieces el juego... - Mátalo.
'Would you rather?'
'¿qué prefieres?'
I would rather finish cumming.
Prefiero terminar corriéndome.
And if your neck hurts that much, get a chiropractor."
Y si te duele tanto el cuello, visita a un quiropráctico".
"May your wife be barren."
"Ojalá tu mujer sea estéril".
- No. - No, I wouldn't go there.
- No. - No, eso no.
"The wrath of God,
"La ira de Dios,
and all the goddesses and gods in the forests and in our lands.
y de todos los dioses de los bosques y de nuestras tierras.
- Fuck yeah. - May you be cursed...
- Eso. - Así te maldigan...
- Yes. - And may you beg for mercy...
...y ruegues por la misericordia que nunca tendrás".
That was awesome, Kaylie.
Qué pasada, Kaylie.
- Time to do this. Ready? - Yes, let's do this.
- Hora de enviarlo. - ¿Lista?
Do we need to spell-check?
¿Revisamos ortografía?
- No. Fuck it. - No.
No. A la mierda.
On the count of three, all right?
A la de tres.
- One... - Yes.
- Uno.. - Sí.
- Two.
- Dos.
- Three.
- Tres.
- What's going on? - Sorry. I'm stealing Wi-Fi.
- ¿Qué pasa? - Robo wifi.
Can you get closer to the window?
Acércalo a la ventana.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Claro.
Now my mom's calling from a blocked number.
Mi madre desde un número desconocido.
- Mom, I told you... - What's happening?
- Mamá... - ¿Qué ocurre?
He hasn't called yet.
No ha llamado.
Mom... Wait, I can't hear you. Hello?
Espera, no te oigo. ¿Hola?
Wes, is that you? It's Jared.
Wes, ¿eres tú? Soy Jared.
Can you hear me? I have a bad connection. I'm in Mexico.
¿Me oyes? No te oigo bien. ¡Estoy en México!
So, what? You're, like, calling me from some beach?
¿Y qué? ¿Me estás llamando desde una playa?
No, I'm in the hospital.
No, desde el hospital.
bruised a lung,
me perforé un pulmón y me fracturé alguna vértebra.
Yeah, they had me in a medically-induced coma.
Me tenían en un coma inducido.
- You were in a coma? - Yeah.
- ¿Estabas en coma? - Sí.
- Fuck. - I have this client, Mauricio Sanchez,
Tenía a un cliente, Mauricio Sanchez,
a big soccer star. Anyway, he got arrested on Saturday.
una estrella del fútbol... Lo detuvieron.
- Had to fly to Cabo to deal with it. - I'm fucked. Stop!
- Vine para solucionarlo. - ¡Parad!
Oh, no. I feel so awful.
Me siento fatal.
No, I do.
No, eso yo.
I can't believe we haven't talked for five days.
No hemos hablado en cinco días.
You weren't pissed off, were you?
No te has cabreado, ¿no?
What? No, no, no.
¿Eh? Qué va.
Wes, thanks for being so cool about me not calling.
Gracias por tomártelo así.
- Fuckers. - Most girls would've freaked out.
Muchas chicas se habrían asustado.
You know me. It takes a lot to get me worked up. Pfft.
Ya me conoces. Cuesta mucho enfadarme.
Yeah, I know. That's what I love about you.
Es lo que me gusta de ti.
You're so reasonable.
Eres muy sensata.
Might be the last normal girl left in LA.
Ya no quedan chicas normales.
- Can I call you back, Jar? - What? No.
- Te llamo en un momento. - No.
No. My phone's at the casita, back at the Las Playas resort.
No. Mi teléfono está en la casita, en el complejo Las Playas.
- They won't let me have my work stuff. - Oh, my God.
No me dejan coger las cosas.
They just want me to rest.
Solo descanso.
I'll call you when I know more, all right? I miss you.
Te llamo cuando sepa algo, ¿vale? Te echo de menos.
I miss you too. God.
Yo también te echo de menos. Joder.
- Success tastes good.
Qué bien sabe el éxito.
- Success tastes sweet. - Don't send it. He was
Estaba en coma.
- in a coma! - The e-mail sent!
¡Enviado!
Wait, what did you say?
¿Qué has dicho?
Jared was in a coma?
¿Estaba en coma?
Yes, since Tuesday, in Mexico.
Sí, desde el martes, en México.
Wh-What was the thing you said right before that?
¿Qué has dicho antes?
- What did she say? - We sent the e-mail.
- ¿Qué ha dicho? - Enviamos el correo.
What?
¿Cómo?
Well, that's what you told us to do.
Es lo que nos dijiste.
- No. - Oh, my God.
- No. - Madre mía.
- I'm gonna pass away.
- Dios mío. - Me desmayo.
Just... I'm gonna just... pass away.
Me va... a dar algo.
- Now, let me go. I'm dead. - No, no, no, no, no.
- Dejadme. Estoy muerta. - No.
Oh, I have an idea.
Tengo una idea.
We'll just send him another e-mail.
Le enviaremos otro correo.
Subject line: "Do not read the last e-mail."
Asunto: "No leas el último correo".
No! What's wrong with you? Don't do that.
¡No! ¿Qué dices? Eso no se hace.
If I got an e-mail saying, "Don't read the last e-mail,"
Si recibiera un correo así, es lo primero que haría.
Fuck, you're right. I'm sorry. I'm drunk.
Perdón. Estoy borracha.
We need to get out of this. Where's the computer?
Hay que solucionar esto, ¿Y el ordenador?
Give me the computer.
Dame el ordenador.
- Give it to me. - Okay. It's gonna be okay.
- Dámelo. - Vale. Todo saldrá bien.
It's gonna be okay. Just write him something really sweet.
Todo irá bien. Escríbele algo bonito.
"My tender heart.
"Mi tierno corazón.
My angel whisperer."
Mi ángel susurrador".
Are you naming Care Bears?
¿Osos Cariñosos?
No, I don't know his password. We've been dating a month.
No. Llevamos un mes.
I knew Dave's by day five. I wouldn't blow him until he told me.
Yo no se la chupé hasta que me lo dijo.
There's gotta be something. Ugh. Think.
Tiene que haber algo. Pensemos.
- What are we gonna do? - What the hell are we gonna do?
¿Qué vamos a hacer?
There's gotta be something we could do.
Algo podremos hacer.
- Just tell him you are possessed. - 'Cause that makes him wanna date me.
- Estás poseída. - No querrá salir conmigo.
- Tell him you love thin dicks. - But I don't.
- Te gustan las pollas finas. - No.
"I have a drinking problem."
"¡Soy alcohólica!"
None of these things are gonna make him want to continue dating me.
Nada de eso hará que quiera salir conmigo.
I... Oh, my God. I don't know. I don't know what to do.
Madre mía. No sé qué podemos hacer.
I mean, the only thing you could do is just go delete the e-mail
Lo único que puedes hacer es borrar el correo
from all of his devices, which are God knows where.
de sus dispositivos. A saber dónde están.
I know where they are. In his hotel room.
En su habitación.
A lot of good that does.
Pues eso no ayuda.
You guys...
Chicas...
I want you to take this really seriously.
quiero que os toméis esto en serio.
Would it be insane if I went to Mexico and erased the e-mail?
¿Sería una locura que fuera a México y borrara el correo?
- Yes. - No.
- Sí. - No.
Kaylie.
Kaylie.
You guys, it could be a fun girls' trip. We could all go.
Podría ser un viaje divertido.
Just the three of us. How fun will that be?
Nosotras tres. ¡Será diver! Hace mucho que no lo hacemos.
- Oh, no. I'm not going to Mexico. - To Mexico?
- No iré a México. - ¿México?
- I can't leave the country right now. - You could have a revenge affair.
- No puedo salir del país. - Podrías vengarte.
Think of how fun that'll be. You deserve it.
Será divertido. Te lo mereces.
You guys, if I go alone, it's stalking. If you're there...
Si voy sola, es acoso. Si estáis ahí...
it's still stalking, but it's also a fun vacation...
lo sigue siendo, pero también vacaciones.
- after this. - Oh, my God.
Madre mía.
- I mean, Ángel has a retreat near Cabo. - Yes.
- Ángel tiene un refugio cerca de Cabo. - Sí.
- Maybe I could go to do that. - Great. Hit that up.
- Podría ir a eso. - Genial.
- Okay. - Perfect. Good reasons are piling up.
- Vale. - Perfecto. Se acumulan buenas razones.
- This is great. - Yeah.
Genial.
I think that you guys are gonna have the best time in Mexico.
Creo que lo pasaréis muy bien en México.
And I am not going anywhere with either of you...
Pero no pienso ir con vosotras,
We're going to Mexico.
- porque es una locura. - Nos vamos a México.
that you do. I hate that when you do that.
Odio que hagas eso.
And don't give me
Y no me pongas
that weird little cat-like grin on your face.
esa sonrisa de gato raro.
Come on, guys. It's one hour of burglary and two days by the pool.
Venga, chicas. Es una hora de robo y dos días en la piscina.
Okay? This is all I have.
Es lo único que tengo.
If Jared reads that e-mail, my life is over...
Si Jared lee el correo, mi vida se ha acabado...
Wesley, stop. Please, just stop.
Basta. Por favor.
Okay, this pitch is fricking horrible,
Vale, me parece una idea terrible,
but I...
pero...
love you, and I do wanna see you happy.
te quiero y quiero verte feliz.
I love you too. Come on.
Yo también te quiero. Venga.
but let's go break into some dude's room.
pero allanemos la casa de ese tío.
My God. That's so...
Madre mía. Es...
Ramon will show you to your casita.
Ramón te guiará.
Enjoy your stay, señora Darya.
Disfrute de su estancia, Sra. Darya.
Uh, before we go up, could you show me which casita
¿Podría enseñarme dónde se hospeda Jared Sterling?
Yeah. Allow me to connect you.
Deje que le llame.
Oh, he's actually not there right now.
No está ahí ahora mismo.
I was hoping I could just slip a little note under his door.
Esperaba poder pasarle una nota por debajo de la puerta.
It's actually against hotel policy to give out room numbers.
No damos números de habitaciones. Seguro que lo entiende.
Uh, sir. I've got the bag... Hold on...
Señor. Tengo la bolsa. Un momento...
Oh, boy.
Vaya.
Whoa, Mom. This is neat.
Mira, mamá. Cómo mola.
He's touching it.
¡Lo está tocando!
Why is it shaking so much?
¿Por qué vibra?
- It feels kinda weird. - Nolan,
- Es raro. - Nolan,
- put that down now. - But it looks funny.
- baja eso. - Parece divertido.
- What kind of toy is this? - Ugh.
¿Qué clase de juguete es este?
- Can't use that again. - Drop it.
No se podrá usar más.
When Mommy says, "Drop it," we drop it.
Si digo "suéltalo", lo sueltas.
Hey, buddy. That's actually my...
Hola, colega. Ese es mi...
little toy.
juguetito.
For a second there, I thought my 12-year-old owned a sex toy.
Pensaba que mi hijo tenía un juguete sexual.
No, it's my dildo.
No, es mío.
What is going on here? Is this a sex resort?
¿Qué pasa aquí? ¿Es un complejo sexual?
- No, this is not... - What?
- No, esto no es... - ¿Qué?
That was not in the brochure!
¡No nos avisaron!
Actually, teaching your child about self-love
Enseñarle a tu hijo amor propio
is a really beautiful gift.
es un regalo muy bonito.
Oh, really?
¿Sí?
I think a beautiful gift is a beautiful vacation,
Un regalo bonito son unas vacaciones
and it's now basically ruined.
y ya se han estropeado.
- I feel like you're mad. - Nolan, let's go.
- ¿Se ha enfadado? - Nolan, vamos.
- Why, Mom? - Come.
- ¿Por qué? - Ven.
- She seemed nice. - Poor kid.
Parecía maja.
- God damn it. - Wow, she came in strong.
- Mierda. - Cómo se ha puesto.
You have complicated things. May we go to our room?
¿Podemos ir ya a nuestra habitación?
- Let's get a drink. - Thank you.
- Vamos a tomar algo. - Gracias.
Gracias. Okay.
Gracias. Entendido.
- This is nice. - Oh, wow.
- Qué bonito. - Caray.
I hope this minibar's a megabar.
Espero que haya un megabar.
Hey, "automatic out" girl.
Oye, chica de la "salida automática".
Come on. What's up?
Venga ya. ¿Qué pasa?
What are you doing here in, uh, Cabo?
¿Qué haces aquí, en Cabo?
Snowboarding.
Snowboard.
That's a weird coincidence. I'm doing the exact same thing.
Qué coincidencia. Yo hago lo mismo.
Yeah, it's totally crazy for two people from LA
Una locura que dos personas de Los Ángeles
to be in Cabo at the same time.
estén en Cabo a la vez.
- Same time. - Has it ever happened before?
- A la vez. - ¿Ha pasado antes?
Probably not. I know. That's why it's so weird.
Probablemente no. Lo sé. Por eso es extraño.
You think I followed you here like a lunatic
¿Crees que te seguí como una loca por obsesión?
No.
No.
I followed someone else here...
He seguido a otra persona
like a lunatic 'cause I'm so obsessed with him.
porque estoy obsesionada con él.
- Oh. You have a new boyfriend? - Mm-hmm.
Ah. ¿Tienes novio?
That's... Congratulations. That's a... I mean, you work fast, but...
Felicidades. Has ido rápido pero...
That's what happens when you give someone more than ten seconds at a bar.
Eso pasa cuando hablas con alguien más de 10 segundos.
- Listen. I've been meaning to call you. - Oh, why?
- Iba a llamarte. - ¿Por qué?
I feel bad about what happened. That's all.
Me siento mal por lo que pasó.
What?
¿Qué?
Oh, you met Q?
¿Conoces a Q?
- Q? - How could I forget?
- ¿Q? - Hombre, claro.
Yes, we did.
Sí.
Oh, good, good, good. Yeah, we went to Cornell together.
Bien. Sí, fuimos juntos a la uni.
- Yeah, he was in the hotel... - You know what, Sean?
- Estaba en el hotel... - ¿Sabes qué?
- No. - No?
- No. - ¿No?
No.
No.
No, you haven't met Q? Or, you...
¿No conoces a Q?
- Just... no. - It's automatic out.
- No. - Es una salida automática.
I deserve that.
Me lo merezco.
- Yeah. This is awesome. - God.
- Es increíble. - Bueno.
There are five restaurants here.
Hay cinco restaurantes.
That was Sean.
Ese era Sean.
- What? - Yeah.
- ¿Qué? - Sí.
What's he doing here?
¿Qué hace aquí?
- That's so random. - I know.
- Qué raro. - Lo sé.
- Isn't that crazy? - Yeah.
- Es muy fuerte. - Sí.
All right. Now...
Vale.
do we think Jared would have requested a view of the beach or the golf course?
¿Jared habrá pedido vistas a la playa o al campo de golf?
What kind of sociopath would request a view of the golf course?
¿Qué sociópata pediría vistas al campo de golf?
Please tell me you have a plan to find Jared's room.
¿Tienes un plan para encontrar la habitación?
Brooke.
Brooke.
- She doesn't have a plan. - She never has a plan.
- No tiene plan. - Nunca tiene un plan.
- Okay.
- Vale.
- So, we just keep dialing Jared's phone... - Yeah.
- ¿Seguimos llamando a Jared. - Sí.
- Until we hear it ringing? - Exactly.
- ...hasta oírlo?
This plan sucks my dick.
Este plan es una mierda.
There's literally 100 casitas.
Hay como 100 casitas.
- We're gonna be at this for days. - Honey, we gotta stay positive.
- Estaremos así durante días. - Positividad.
Okay, wait. Do you guys hear it ringing?
Vale, espera. ¿Oís un timbre?
- No. - This is so annoying.
- No. - Qué mierda.
All I hear is the dumb ocean.
Solo oigo las olas del mar.
Wait. I think I hear something.
Espera. Creo que he oído algo.
Oh, my God. That's his ringtone.
Es su tono de llamada.
Hold up. We flew here for a guy who downloads ringtones?
¿Hemos venido a por un tío que descarga tonos?
Oh, my God. He's being ironic, I assume.
Madre mía. Está siendo irónico, supongo.
This is awesome. It only took... 197 international roaming phone calls
Esto es increíble. Solo he necesitado 197 llamadas internacionales
to find him. Come on.
para encontrarlo.
What do we do?
¿Qué hacemos?
Like, Google breaking and entering? I don't know.
¿Busco cómo allanar una casa? No sé.
Fuck.
Joder.
- Shit. - Okay.
- Mierda. - Vale.
On a scale of one to ten, how desperate are you
En una escala del 1 al 10, ¿cuán desesperada estás?
- I think that's a hard ten. - That could be a 12.
- Parece un diez alto. - O un 12.
All right. How do I look?
Vale. ¿Qué tal estoy?
- Okay, take the tray... very good. - Let's see.
- Vale, coge la bandeja. Muy bien. - A ver.
I really wanna believe you here, and I'm not.
Tengo muchas ganas de creerte, pero no puedo.
- I know. Okay. - I feel like she should be, like,
- Lo sé. Vale. - Deberías estar
extra desperate right now.
mucho más desesperada.
Extra, like, committed to getting in that room.
Más decidida a entrar en la habitación.
I wanna feel that.
Quiero verlo.
- When I see you, I wanna go, "Bam!" - Apologize.
Quiero decir: "Bam".
- Oh, I'm so sorry. - But do not say you're sorry.
- Lo siento mucho. - No digas eso.
But also be, like, sexy.
Pero ponte sexy.
That's hot.
Muy bien.
"Oh, I just got out of the shower, and the door locked behind me."
"He salido de la ducha y se me ha cerrado la puerta".
How would I get wet?
Estoy seca.
- Yeah, like that. - Yeah. I can see it.
- Así. - Puedo verlo.
I'm feeling it better now. We'll leave your clothes by this tree,
Mucho mejor. Dejaremos tu ropa junto al árbol
and then you're gonna come to the bar when you're done.
y cuando acabes, vienes al bar.
- Okay? - Okay.
- ¿Vale? - Vale.
- We love you. - I love you.
- Te queremos. - Os quiero.
- Energy! Commitment! Sexy! - Sell it.
- Energía. Compromiso. ¡Sexy! - Véndelo.
- Yes, and... - I'm gonna try really hard.
Como tú sabes.
- Hola. Las Playas... - Hi, yes. There seems to be a woman
- Hola. Las Playas... - Hay una mujer
who is locked out of her casita, number 34.
que no puede entrar en su casita, número 34.
- Help me! - Yeah, she needs to be let in ASAP.
- ¡Ayuda! - Tiene que ayudarla.
- Of course. We'll be there right away. - Okay, great. Thank you. Bye.
- Vamos de inmediato. - Vale, genial. Gracias. Adiós.
She must really like this guy.
Le gusta de verdad.
I remember those days.
Recuerdo aquella época.
Thank you.
Gracias.
- Cheers.
- Salud.
- Welcome to Brookie's revenge affair. - Oh, no. I just want to get drunk.
- Bienvenidas a la venganza de Brookie. - Solo quiero emborracharme.
All right, what are we gonna do?
Muy bien, ¿qué hacemos?
This.
Esto...
No, I think we're gonna go over to that table.
No, creo que iremos a esa mesa.
Oh, no, I'm just not in a place to go talk to dudes right now.
No estoy en condiciones de hablar con tíos.
Well, you gotta get out of your head and get into your body.
Tienes que salir de tu cabeza y meterte en tu cuerpo.
Yeah, well, my body is telling me to stay right here.
Mi cuerpo me dice que me quede aquí.
- So... - Come over.
Venid.
Well, I'm bringing your body this way,
Voy a llevarte por aquí,
- and you're gonna have some sex. - No. Kaylie, don't...
- y vas a follar. - No. Kaylie...
Oh, God, yeah.
Bueno, vale...
So sorry to bother you, but I was putting my tray down,
Siento molestar. Estaba bajando la bandeja
and the door slammed shut.
y la puerta se cerró.
Señora Darya. This is not your casita.
Señora Darya. Esta no es su casita.
You're right, it is not my casita.
Tiene razón, no es mi casita.
No, this is the casita of this random man that I was love-making with
No, esta es la casita de un hombre con el que hacía el amor.
who went to get ice...
Ha ido a por hielo...
to ice his body...
para su cuerpo...
because the sex we were having was so hard.
porque lo estábamos haciendo muy duro.
But I-I-I can't broke the rules.
Pero no puedo romper las reglas.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes, yes. Si, si, si..
Sí.
Come on.
Vamos.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Por favor.
I'm begging you. I'm begging you.
Te lo suplico.
- Ramon, please. - Okay.
- Ramón, por favor. - Está bien.
- Okay, I do it. But don't cry, please. - Yes! I love you!
- Vale. Pero no llore. - ¡Te quiero!
- Don't cry. Be quiet. - I'm not gonna cry.
- No llore. - No lloro.
- Be quiet. - Thank you.
- Silencio. - Gracias.
- Okay.
- Vale.
Come in.
Adelante.
Thank you so much, Ramon. Thank you.
Muchas gracias. Gracias.
- Yeah, okay, okay, okay... - Thank you.
- Sí, vale. - Gracias.
- Bye.
- Adiós.
Thank you. Bye.
Gracias. Adiós.
Oh, yes. Yes. Okay.
Vale...
Oh, yes.
Sí.
What?
¿Qué?
- Wow, you're here? - What are you doing here?
- ¿Estás aquí?. - ¿Qué haces aquí?
This is my room.
Esta es mi habitación.
No, this is my boyfriend's room.
No, esta es la habitación de mi novio.
You know it is.
Eso digo.
Though I'm very flattered, this is not anything.
Aunque me siento muy halagada, esto no es nada.
Okay.
Vale.
Wait.
Un momento.
- Shit. I'm supposed to be in that room. - You don't have to pretend, Miss Wesley.
- Mierda. Esta habitación no es. - No tiene que fingir, señorita Wesley.
I know why you're here.
Sé por qué está aquí.
What?
¿Qué?
I googled your pink penis toy.
Busqué en Google su pene rosa.
It's called a vibrator, and it's for girls who are lonely.
Es un vibrador y es para chicas que se sienten solas.
What the hell are you talking about? Just get out...
¿De qué narices hablas? Vete...
I completely respect you, and, look, my eyes are completely closed,
La respeto totalmente y por eso tengo los ojos cerrados.
I'm just gonna give this to you without any lawsuit.
Le voy a dar esto sin denunciarla.
Oh, my... oh, my God.
Madre mía.
- What the fuck is going on here? - Wait!
- ¿Qué coño pasa aquí? - ¡Espera!
Schmoops! Are you okay? Eye contact!
¡Oye! ¿Estás bien? ¡Contacto visual!
I'm amazing. Yeah.
Estoy muy bien, sí.
What's it like to be in sales?
¿Cómo es trabajar en ventas?
Ugh. God, it is the worst.
Es lo peor.
We're just in all-day workshops about how to market boner pills.
Todo el día haciendo talleres de cómo vender pastillas para erecciones.
Do they really call them "boner pills"?
¿Así las llamáis?
Technically, the name is "Bonalis,"
Técnicamente, la marca se llama "Empalmina".
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Perdón. Lo siento.
Why does the world need more boner pills?
No necesitamos más pastillas para eso.
Am I right?
¿Verdad?
I mean, can't we just invent a drug that keeps a guy's dick in his pants?
Mejor una droga para que los tíos mantengan la polla en los pantalones.
- Can you do that? - I'll work on it.
- ¿No? - Lo intentaré.
Thank you. Oh, what about...?
Gracias. ¿Y...?
Could you actually make a good dick GPS?
¿Podrías hacer un GPS para pollas?
So that way, when a dick is going in another woman,
Si está con otra mujer,
it sets off this little switch that just fries his pecker right off.
se activa un interruptor y le fríe la polla.
- That sounds like a human rights crime. - Right?
- Suena a delito. - ¿Verdad?
- Seems harsh. - That's pretty funny.
- Parece duro. - Qué gracioso.
- Thank you. - I mean, maybe not the best joke...
- Gracias. - No es el mejor chiste
to make when you wanna pick me up or anything, but...
si quieres ligar conmigo.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Perdona.
You thought that I was trying to pick you up?
¿Creías que quería ligar contigo?
- I'm sorry, what else are we doing here? - I'm sorry.
- ¿Qué estamos haciendo si no? - Perdona.
It's just, you're wearing man-sandals and like five million bracelets.
Es que llevas sandalias y cinco millones de pulseras.
I told you just to pick one bracelet.
Con una bastaba.
I can't pick just one bracelet. They're all fucking cool.
No puedo elegir una pulsera. Molan mucho.
Should've picked one.
Una mejor.
I was kinda getting the vibe that you may be DTF when we sat down.
Creía que te habías sentado porque querías follar.
But you also seem to have, like, a darkness and a sadness about you,
Pero también tienes un aura de oscuridad y tristeza,
and it's, like, a real turnoff.
y me corta el rollo.
I feel like I was a bit misled.
Me siento engañado.
I already took a Bonalis, so...
Me he tomado una Empalmina, así que...
I'm... gonna have to nurse this boner here pretty soon.
voy a tener que ordeñar a la serpiente pronto.
Oh, really? What hand are you gonna use?
¿En serio? ¿Con qué mano?
The one with all the bracelets all over it?
¿La de las pulseras?
Well, what are you gonna do? You gonna... finger yourself in that pantsuit?
¿Qué harás? ¿Te masturbarás con esa ropa?
- I mean, come on. - Jesus.
- Venga ya. - Joder.
Yeah, I'm gonna jack off with these bracelets.
Sí, me voy correr con estas pulseras.
And I guess I'm gonna have to take it to the pool
Tendré que ir a la piscina
because I don't have a chest to jizz on tonight.
porque no tengo un pecho en el que correrme.
- All right, I'm out. - Right.
- Me voy. - Vale.
Said my piece.
Ya lo he dicho.
Time to jerk.
A pajearse.
- Oh, my God. - Oh my...
Madre mía.
- What?
- Madre mía. - ¿Qué?
That's a really small plate.
Es muy pequeño.
It's the biggest plate they have!
Es lo que hay.
I'm so sorry about that.
Lo siento mucho.
He's going through a custody battle right now...
Quiere la custodia de sus hijos.
Well, he technically gave up his kids.
Bueno, los abandonó.
Listen, I love you.
Mira, me encantas.
- I love you too. - I'm gonna put you in my pocket
Te metería en el bolsillo
and take you back to Cleveland with me.
y te llevaría conmigo.
- Please. - Find me at the resort, okay?
Búscame en el complejo.
- I'm going to. - Bye.
- Eso haré. - Adiós.
- Okay. - Oh, I found a friend.
- Vale. - He hecho un amigo.
Congratulations.
Enhorabuena.
Oh, God.
Joder.
No.
No.
Shit.
Mierda.
Sweetie, you're not very good at revenge affairs,
No se te dan muy bien las venganzas,
but that guy was a fucking asshole.
pero ese tío era un capullo.
Thank you.
Gracias.
Yeah, I don't wanna just, like, have sex with anybody, okay?
Sí, no quiero sexo con nadie, ¿vale?
I mean, I haven't even...
Hace por lo menos...
broken the seal in like a year.
un año que no lo hago.
Whoa, you haven't had sex in a year?
¿Llevas un año sin hacerlo?
What am I supposed to do, Kaylie?
¿Qué hago, Kaylie?
I mean, do I divorce Dave?
¿Me divorcio de Dave?
Or do I forgive him?
¿O le perdono?
Is murder on the table?
¿Lo puedo matar?
- Oh, no, no, no. - Five minutes,
- No. - Cinco minutos.
you'll get clarity, I'll get a baby.
tú lucidez y yo un bebé.
Wait, they give you a baby in five minutes?
¿Cómo? ¿Te dan un bebé en cinco minutos?
Yes. It's a very quick gestation period.
Sí. Es un periodo de gestación muy rápido.
Hey, you guys.
Hola, chicas.
I'll explain it in the room. Go.
Os lo explico de camino.
- Go. Get up. - What is happening?
- Levantaos. - ¿Qué está pasando?
- Go, get up! Go. - Okay.
- ¡Arriba! - Vale.
- Come on. - Freeze!
- Venga. - ¡Alto!
You come into my casita and put your hands on my child?
¿Vienes a mi casita y le pones las manos encima?
- What are you? A pedophile? - Whoa!
- ¿Eres una pederasta? - No soy una pederasta.
This is what you do? You go to second base with children?
¿Te va eso? ¿Tocar niños?
Didn't mean for him to touch my boob.
No quería que me tocara.
You think I wanted that?
No quería esto.
I'm not interested in your kid.
No me interesa.
I understand Nolan is very desirable and he has a very bright future.
Entiendo que es deseable y tiene un futuro brillante.
I'm not attracted to your child. No offense, but I'm really not.
No me atrae su hijo. Sin ofender, pero no.
Mom, she didn't do it. Both of us felt love.
Mamá, no fue así. Los dos queríamos.
Shut up. You're making it worse.
Calla. Lo empeoras.
Stay away, whorebag,
No te acerques, guarra,
or I will pop you like a balloon.
o te reventaré como un globo.
Come on. Let's get you a quesadilla.
Vamos a por una quesadilla.
Get your life together.
¡Comportaos!
- Oh, God. Wesley? - Whore-shaming is not cool.
- ¿Wesley? - Eso no ha molado.
Where are your clothes?
¿Y tu ropa?
There's... What're you looking at?
¿Qué miran?
Yoo-hoo!
¡Hola!
Good morning!
¡Buenos días!
Wow. Volume.
¡Caray! Cuánto ruido.
Somebody's not in a real vacationy mood, it seems.
Alguien no está de muy buen humor.
Someone flashed 50 guests butt naked,
Enseñé el culo a 50 personas,
is now an accused pedophile, and also, Jared will hate me if he gets this e-mail.
ahora soy una pederasta y Jared me odiará si lee el correo.
We've been doing recon all morning,
Llevamos toda la mañana,
and we figured out a way to get into Jared's room.
sabemos cómo entrar en la habitación.
Oh, my God. How?
Madre mía. ¿Cómo?
Twice a week, Quintano takes the guests paddleboarding,
Cada semana, Quintano va a remar
and when he goes in, he leaves all of his shit on the shore.
y deja todas sus cosas en la orilla.
So...
Así que...
Oh, so we just have to grab the master key from his clothes while he's in the ocean.
tenemos que cogerle la llave maestra mientras está en el mar.
All right, Q. Let's dance.
Vale, Q. Vamos a bailar.
- Habla anglés? - Paddleboard?
- ¿Me entiende? - ¿Remo?
Ain't that cute? Saving me a seat.
Qué mona. Me guarda un sitio.
Why are you here? No one invited you to sit down.
¿Quién te ha dicho que te sientes?
Well, I missed my van this morning.
Perdí la caravana.
And so, I couldn't drag myself out of bed.
Y no podía levantarme de la cama.
And now, I get to see you.
Y ahora me encuentro contigo.
What are you here for? What do you want? How can I get rid of you quicker?
¿A qué has venido? ¿Cómo puedo librarme de ti?
I'm here to go paddleboarding, with you, actually.
Vengo a hacer paddle surf contigo.
Oh, I'm not going.
No voy a ir.
- Are you ready? - Oh! That's us. Come on, let's go.
- ¿Listos? - Va para nosotros. Vamos.
- Hmm? No. - Yeah.
- No. - Sí.
- No. - What do you mean?
- ¿Qué quieres decir?
I'll hang back while my friends go in.
Irán mis amigas. Las dos. Tú no eres mi amigo.
- Hi, Kaylie and I can't go paddleboarding. - Hey.
- Hola, Kaylie y yo no podemos ir a remar. - Hola.
Why?
¿Por qué?
They dinged me for my asthma.
No me dejan por el asma.
And I checked the box that said I may be pregnant.
Y yo dije que podría estar embarazada.
I wanted to feel what it was like. Sorry.
Quería saber qué se sentía.
- Why would you do that? - Sean!
- ¿Por qué? - Sean!
Señoras, may I zinc on your face?
Señoras, ¿un poco de crema?
- What? - You wanna zinc on my face?
- ¿Qué? - ¿Es zinc?
How many times I gotta tell you, Ramon?
¿Cuántas veces debo decirlo?
Not on my face. On my back, maybe. I'll see y'all in the water.
En la cara no. En la espalda, quizá. Os veo en el agua.
- He's fun. - Actually, right here,
En realidad,
Wesley loves it when people zinc all over her face.
a Wesley le encanta el zinc en la cara.
You're not funny.
Qué gracia.
- It's kinda true. - You're not funny.
- Es verdad. - No.
- It's a little funny. - No... Oh, Ramon, it's okay. No.
- Un poco sí. - No, Ramon, no te preocupes.
Thank you, thank you.
Gracias.
Kidding. She's kidding around, joking. Muy loco.
Es broma. Está bromeando.
Okay. Bye.
Entendido. Adiós.
Thank you. No one will be going in the water.
Nadie se meterá en el agua.
Oh, no. Actually, we have to.
Tenemos que hacerlo.
Quintano said that if none of us go paddleboarding,
Si ninguna se apunta a la clase,
he's gotta drive us back.
nos lleva de vuelta por haber desaprovechado las plazas.
Yeah, come on, Wesley, we just gotta steal Quintano's keys.
Sí, tenemos que robar la llave de Quintano.
Okay, please don't scream that, Kaylie.
No grites eso, Kaylie.
- I am getting too emotionally involved. - Kaylie, you're...
- Me estoy involucrando demasiado - Kaylie,
- I'm not happy right now. - You got this. Let's go.
- no me gusta esto. - Irá bien.
- Just want you to know that. - You're gonna be great.
- Tenlo en mente.. - Irá genial.
- I have to hang out with Sean now. - I'm jealous.
- Voy con Sean. - Qué envidia.
- Awesome. - I wanted to go.
- Genial. - Yo quería ir.
- Enjoy yourself! - I don't like this person.
- ¡Disfruta! - No me gusta.
- We love you! - The ocean is a gift, beauty!
- ¡Te queremos! - ¡El mar es un regalo, belleza!
I hate being wet!
¡Odio mojarme!
What is this, tequila?
¿Qué es esto? ¿Tequila?
Well, well, well. Look who decided to join us.
Mira quién se nos une.
Ah. Are we on a schedule? Jesus.
¿Vamos bien de tiempo? Joder.
Okay, no more dilly-dally. Let's go.
Vale, basta de tonterías. Vamos.
Sean, you're paddling too fast. Wait for me!
Vas demasiado rápido. ¡Espérame!
Wait, I think we're supposed to be standing on these.
Espera, creo que debemos estar de pie.
You think I'm gonna stand up on this thing? Nah.
¿Que me ponga de pie? No.
Okay, good. I'm so tired, I don't wanna stand either.
Estoy muy cansada. No puedo.
- Cheers.
- Salud.
- I'm actually into this dock situation. - Yeah.
- Me gusta esta zona. - Sí.
- Who set this up? - Well, could be one of two things.
- ¿Quién lo ha montado? - Una de dos.
Ramon parachutes down
Ramon en paracaídas
from his two-bedroom brick bungalow in the sky.
desde su casa en el cielo.
Two, your imaginary boyfriend.
Dos, tu novio imaginario.
- He sets all this up. - My boyfriend's not imaginary.
- Ha sido él. - Mi novio no es imaginario.
So, he's a ghost?
¿Es un fantasma?
Well, almost.
Bueno, casi.
I sent Jared a really mean e-mail
Le envié a Jared un correo muy cruel
because I thought he had ghosted me.
porque creía que me ignoraba.
I didn't hear from him for a few days, and it turns out he had not ghosted me
No he sabido nada de él en unos días, y resulta que...
but was in a coma... here.
estaba en coma.
So, you're here to, like, apologize or something like that, or...
¿Has venido a disculparte...?
Well, I came here to break into his room and delete the e-mail.
Bueno, a entrar en su habitación para borrar el correo.
Right after I met you...
Después de conocerte...
- Uh-oh. - Oh, my God, a dolphin.
Madre mía, un delfín.
Oh, my God. Look! Hi!
Madre mía. ¡Mira! ¡Hola!
This is so amazing! Look at how close he is to us.
¡Es alucinante! Mira qué cerca está.
Mm-mm, no. nah. See, you on your own with this one.
No. Esto para ti solita.
Aww, look at him. He's smiling at you.
Míralo. Te está sonriendo.
Really? You know, dolphins smile no matter what.
Los delfines sonríen siempre.
That's the way their face is shaped.
Su cara es así.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Madre mía.
Oh, shit!
¡Mierda!
Oh, no.
No.
- He's hugging me! - No, no, no!
- ¡Me está abrazando! - ¡No!
My dog hugged my leg, too. But for a whole different reason.
Mi perro lo hacía. Por otra razón.
Get my camera, I wanna post this! Hi!
Hazme una foto, quiero publicar esto. ¡Hola!
Don't look him in his eye. They like that shit.
No le mires a los ojos.
What-What-What... What was that?
¿Qué ha sido eso?
- That was a hug, right? - You need a cigarette?
- ¿Era un abrazo? - ¿Quieres un cigarro?
That was intense.
Ha sido intenso.
Where'd you go, little guy?
¿Adónde has ido, monada?
- Oh, my God! - Oh, God.
- Madre mía. - Joder.
- Are you okay? - What the hell just happened?
¿Qué ha pasado?
I thought we were playing.
¿No era un juego?
Playing? Ah! Nah, y'all weren't playing.
No, no estabais jugando.
- Was that his dick? - I'll be honest with you... yeah.
- ¿Era su polla? - Te diré la verdad.
God, I feel sick!
Joder, me encuentro mal.
- Oh, my God, Wes! - Hey!
- Madre mía. - ¡Hola!
- Why did he do that to me? - 'Cause you're very sexy.
- ¿Por qué me hizo eso? - Eres muy sexy.
- Hey, are you okay? - Sweetie.
- ¿Estás bien? - Cariño.
- Thank you so much. - It's okay. I'm gonna get a lifeguard.
- Gracias. - Voy a buscar un socorrista.
Okay. What happened?
Vale. ¿Qué ha pasado?
- His dick touched my face. - What?
La polla en la cara.
His dick touched my face.
Me tocó la cara.
I'm sorry. No, I'm really sorry.
Lo siento mucho.
That must have been, like, really traumatic. I'm sorry.
Debe de haber sido traumático.
It was a great distraction. Because...
Ha sido una gran distracción. Porque…
- You got the master key? - Yes!
- ¿Tenéis la llave maestra? - ¡Sí!
What's that smell?
¿A qué huele?
Hey, changed your mind, huh?
Has cambiado de idea.
Turn around, bracelet bitch.
El rey de las pulseras.
- There's the darkness. - Text me later.
- El aura. - Escríbeme luego.
Guys, we need to hurry. We need to get back to Jared's room
Hay que darse prisa. Vayamos a la habitación
before Quintano discovers the key is missing.
antes de que se entere Quintano.
- Sluts. - What?
- Zorras. - ¿Qué?
You guys, I really don't feel good.
Chicas, no me siento bien.
Uh, I think maybe you just drank a little too much seawater.
Has bebido demasiada agua de mar.
- Yeah, I think I'll... - Okay, sweetie?
- Sí, creo que... - ¿Vale?
Stand back, everyone! I learned CPR at fat camp.
¡Apartaos! Aprendí a hacer la RCP en el campamento para gordos.
Does this seem right?
¿Es lo correcto?
Clearing her airway!
¡Despejando la vía!
She needs more air!
¡Necesita más aire!
- Help! - Get off me, you tiny pervert!
- ¡Ayuda! - ¡Suéltame, pequeño pervertido!
Help! Ayuda! These women are attacking my son!
¡Socorro! ¡Están abusando de mi hijo!
- What did I tell you? - She had her mouth on his mouth.
- ¿Qué te he dicho? - Tenía la boca en su boca.
We're in love, Mom.
Estoy enamorado, mamá.
She's my lady.
Es mi chica.
Love? No, we're not in love.
¿Cómo? No, no estamos enamorados.
Fucking A, Mom! Why you always gotta be all up in my shit?
¡Joder, mamá! ¿Por qué te metes en mis cosas?
Nolan Ryan Phillipe, shut it!
Nolan Ryan Phillipe, ¡cállate!
- We had something good going. - Zip it!
- Teníamos algo. - ¡Calla!
- What is wrong with you? - No!
- ¿Qué le pasa? - ¡No!
- Why would you do that? - Oh, you wanna step to me?
- ¿Por qué ha hecho eso? - ¿Me respondes?
I had a 46-hour labor with this one, do you understand?
Tuve un parto de 46 horas, ¿lo entiendes?
I had an episiotomy
Con una episiotomía
that was 18 inches long.
de 45 cm incluida.
You wanna feel pain? I'll show you...
¿Quieres dolor? Ya verás.
- Oh, God. - Ugh.
Madre mía.
- It's gross. - Okay.
- Qué asco. - Vale.
It stinks so bad.
Huele fatal.
- Eighteen inches? - That's a foot and a half.
- ¿45 cm? - Eso es mucho.
I cannot believe I'm saying this,
No me creo que vaya a decir esto,
but I am not attracted to children.
pero no me atraen los niños.
Since you have arrived,
Desde que llegó
you have exposed a child to a vicious sex device,
le expuso a un dispositivo sexual,
you broke into one of my rooms, you ran naked through my restaurant,
se metió en una de mis habitaciones, corrió desnuda por ahí...,
and you, you brought a dolphin to climax.
y se ha acostado con un delfín.
Okay, none of those were my fault. And you should not blame the victim.
Nada de eso fue culpa mía. No culpes a la víctima.
If you enter this resort again, I will have you thrown in jail.
Si vuelve a entrar en este complejo, irá la cárcel.
And let me assure you, your dildo will not be let in.
Y le aseguro que sin consolador.
Okay.
Vale.
Come on, guys. We've only been here one night.
Solo hemos estado aquí una noche.
Let's get our energy up and get back over there.
Hay que coger fuerzas y volver.
- What are you talking about? - We have the master key.
- ¿De qué hablas? - Tenemos la llave maestra.
We gotta go back before they change the code.
Hay que ir cuanto antes.
- Sweetie, um, I think we need to chat. - Oh, no.
- Creo que tenemos que hablar. - No.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Vale. - Gracias.
The energy of this place is a little scary.
La energía de este lugar da miedo.
It's kinda like the universe is sending us a sign.
El universo nos envía una señal.
Yes. Saying, "Get the fuck out."
Sí. Nos dice: "Iros de aquí ya".
Guys, we didn't come this far to only come this far.
Chicas, no hemos venido tan lejos para llegar hasta aquí.
We gotta get that bag...
Hay que encontrar la bolsa...
and we have to delete that e-mail.
y borrar ese correo.
I am begging you. This is what friends do for each other.
Os lo ruego. Es lo que hacen las amigas.
You know? Think of all the times I've been there for you.
Yo os he ayudado montones de veces.
You are way above this emotional blackmail.
Deja ese chantaje emocional.
I don't think I am.
No es chantaje.
I don't wanna eat this.
No quiero esto.
Give me the key.
Dame la llave.
- No. - Brooke.
- No. - Brooke.
- You're not the boss of the key, Brooke.
- No eres la dueña de la llave.
I am the key boss right now,
Ahora mando yo
and the key boss is saying that you cannot go back to that hotel,
y digo que no puedes volver a ese hotel,
so there.
así que...
Brooke, I know how to get it from you.
Sé cómo conseguirla.
Oh, bring it.
Venga.
Please don't get physical.
No le pegues.
- It's not my fault if she pees. - Just...
Si se mea, no es mi culpa.
- I'm coming in. - Don't bring it in.
- Voy. - No lo hagas.
- Don't get physical. - Stop.
- No conseguirás la llave. - No pegues.
- Oh, Brooke. - She's gonna tinkle. Stop! Don't!
- Brooke. - Se va a mear. ¡Para!
Put your hand on the bed!
- Quita las manos. - Te dije que lo conseguiría.
Fuck.
Joder.
Thanks for nothing, guys.
Gracias por nada.
I will remember this betrayal when I pick your bridesmaids dresses.
Recordaré esta traición cuando escoja los vestidos de dama de honor.
They will be hideous...
Serán horribles
and very expensive.
y muy caros.
I will still look amazing in that dress.
Me quedará genial el vestido igualmente.
You're gonna look like shit in this dress.
Te quedará como la mierda.
Wesley. Wes.
Wesley. Wes.
We've all lost our minds.
Se nos ha ido la pinza.
Wesley.
Wesley.
I wish I wasn't so ticklish.
Es muy sensible.
God damn it!
¡Mierda!
She's still not answering. Maybe we should go back.
Sigue sin contestar. Deberíamos volver.
You know what?
Mira,
Why don't we just let her do what she wants?
que haga lo que quiera.
I mean, she doesn't even listen to us, anyway.
Si ni siquiera nos escucha.
Was that the sound of a chainsaw cutting through bone?
¿Eso era una motosierra seccionando miembros?
Okay. We're out.
Larguémonos de aquí.
Come on, you got this.
Vamos, tú puedes.
Shit! Shit! Burn! Burn! Ow!
¡Mierda! ¡Quema!
It's burning me. Ow, shit!
¡Quema! Joder.
What's up, Wes?
¿Qué tal?
Where you going?
¿Adónde vas?
Yes.
Bien.
Oh, my God. Come on. Come on, come on, come on.
Madre mía. Venga.
Where's his e-mail?
¿Dónde está su correo?
- Hi. Hello? - Hey, me again.
- Hola. ¿Diga? - Hola, yo otra vez.
Hi. How are you?
Hola. ¿Cómo estás?
Uh, really good, actually. The doctors are letting me out early.
Muy bien. Me dejarán salir pronto.
No way.
Sí, hombre.
How early?
¿Muy pronto?
Tomorrow, baby.
Mañana, cariño.
What?
¿Qué?
Can you pick me up from the airport?
¿Me recoges en el aeropuerto?
I might be on the late flight.
Cogeré el último vuelo.
Señora Darya!
¡Señora Darya!
- We know you are in there. Open the door. - Sounds like people are yelling.
- Sabemos que estás ahí. Abre. - Hay gente gritando.
- You all right? - Señora Darya, open the door.
- ¿Está bien? - Abra la puerta.
Definitely. The neighbors are doing construction.
Sí, los vecinos están de obras.
What? At night? That's annoying.
¿Por la noche?
Um, yeah. That's okay. I think they're almost finished.
No pasa nada. Casi han terminado.
I would love to pick you up in Los Angeles tomorrow.
Me encantaría recogerte mañana en Los Ángeles.
Okay, I'll text you my flight details when I have them.
Te envío los detalles del vuelo cuando los tenga.
Señora Darya! I know you are here, señora Darya.
¡Señora Darya! Sé que está ahí, señora Darya.
Oh, and, Wes...
Ah, y Wes...
wear something easily removable.
ponte algo fácil de quitar.
Oh, my God! That's so fun! I have to go.
¡Madre mía! ¡Qué divertido! Tengo que dejarte.
Ramon. Ramon.
Ramon.
You can do this.
Puedes hacerlo.
Holy shit! She came for me.
¡Joder! Ha venido a por mí,
This is too much.
Esto es demasiado.
You better get running, 'cause I'm coming.
Será mejor que te vayas, voy par allá.
Ow! My balls! Ramon, I crushed my huevitos.
¡Mis pelotas! Ramon, me he aplastado los huevitos.
- Hi. - Hola.
Hola.
We're just here to get our friend. We were guests here.
Venimos a por nuestro amiga.
We just need to go through.
Tenemos que pasar.
Q, this is crazy, bro.
Qué pasada.
She's trespassing, and she broke in to that man's room.
Entró sin permiso en su habitación.
Listen to Sean. You got...
Escuchad a Sean.
What are you guys doing? I'm just, I'm just in love.
¿Qué estáis haciendo? Estoy muy enamorada.
So, we just need to go in for, just, you know...
Tenemos que ir a...
- You're gonna be okay. - Wait, Kaylie!
- Todo irá bien. - ¡Kaylie!
Oh, my God. Wesley?
Madre mía. ¿Wesley?
Hey. No. I'm just... Dude, get your...
Oiga... No. Solo...
I told you what would happen if you came back,
Le dije lo que pasaría si volvía
and now it's happening.
y está pasando.
Enjoy Mexican jail.
Disfrute.
Kaylie!
¡Kaylie!
Hey! Get out of here! That's not cool!
¡Eh! ¡Fuera de aquí! Eso no mola.
Please... let me just... It's a misunderstanding.
Por favor... Ha sido un malentendido.
Señor? Please, sir!
¡Por favor, señor!
I swear to God, when I get out, I'm gonna take this to social media.
Juro por Dios que cuando salga, lo llevaré a las redes sociales.
Oh, my God. You guys are here. Can you get me out?
Por fin llegáis. ¿Podéis sacarme?
Yes, that's why we are here.
- Para eso estamos aquí. - Ese era el plan.
Now, I don't know, 'cause at least you're contained here.
Pero desde aquí no puedes liarla.
Very funny.
Muy gracioso.
- Sweetie, this is disgusting. - I know.
- Esto da asco. - Ya.
It is. Don't touch the things.
Sí. ¡No toques nada!
It was the wildest shit you've seen.
Ha sido una locura.
- Wait, Sean's here? - Yeah. He brought us here.
- ¿Está Sean? - Sí. Nos trajo él.
- Hello. - What up, Suge Knight?
- Hola. - ¿Cómo va por aquí?
Wow. I like what you've done with the place.
Me gusta cómo has decorado tu casa.
So, got some good news. The good news is that
Buenas noticias.
the hotel is dropping all the charges.
El hotel no te denuncia.
So, you, my friend, are free to go.
Así que puedes salir.
- Was there a bribe? - Daddy took care of it.
- ¿Soborno? - Papá se encargó.
And just so we're clear. In this scenario, I'm not "Daddy."
Que quede claro. No me refiero a mí.
"Daddy" is Nolan.
Fue Nolan.
Nolan, Nolan, Nolan.
Nolan.
- That little boy you've been seeing. - Yep. Yeah, the kid who...
- El chico al que ves. - Sí, el niño que...
Sidebar, I did not think that little kid was your type.
No creo que fuera tu tipo.
But apparently, he cares about you so damn much,
Pero parece que se preocupa tanto por ti
he couldn't stand to see his baby locked up.
que no soportaba verte encerrada.
- I'm not his baby. - That little boy loves you.
- No soy suya. - Te quiere.
I need you to stop talking about Nolan.
Deja de hablar de Nolan.
- We need to talk. - Oh, thank God.
- Hablemos. - Por fin.
Remember you told us we should tell you if you were being unreasonable?
Debíamos avisarte si no atendías a razones.
Look, I know this has been nuts, okay?
Ya sé que esto ha sido una locura.
I can't believe I spent two days trying to break into Jared's room
Llevo dos días intentando entrar en su habitación
when all I had to do was tell him
cuando solo tengo que decirle
I don't think he should fly alone in his condition,
que no debería volar solo,
wait till he falls asleep on the plane, grab his devices,
esperar a que se duerma, coger sus dispositivos,
scan his unconscious face to unlock them, and delete the e-mails.
escanear su cara y borrar los correos.
- It's, like, so easy. - Wesley, stop.
- Es muy fácil. - Wesley, basta.
Can you look at where you are right now. You're in a Mexican jail.
¿Sabes dónde estás? En una cárcel de México.
What do you want me to do? Dwell on that or rise above it?
¿Qué hago? ¿Me mortifico o lo supero?
Dwell on it. Take it in.
Mortifícate. Piense un poco.
This is something you need to process, at the very least for our sanity.
Tienes que procesarlo, aunque sea por nuestra cordura.
Yeah. You are in a relationship
Estás en una relación en la que tienes que mentir todo el rato.
Is that something that you really want?
¿De verdad quieres eso?
Fine. I don't need you guys, okay?
No necesito vuestra ayuda, ¿vale?
I can do this by myself. Sean, help me.
Puedo hacerlo sola. Sean, ayúdame.
- Can we talk about this for a second? - Wesley, you know what?
- ¿Podemos hablarlo? - Wesley.
We love you, but we're done.
Te queremos, pero se acabó.
And you should be done, too.
Deberías dejarlo.
Kaylie and I, we're gonna go,
Kaylie y yo nos vamos
and we're gonna have a really fantastic day in Mexico.
y vamos a tener un día fantástico en México.
Can we go see Ángel?
¿Podemos ir a ver a Ángel?
Fuck, yeah, we can go see Ángel,
Pues claro que iremos a ver a Ángel y meditaremos como condenadas.
I'm getting pregnant. Bye. Sorry.
Voy a embarazarme. Adiós. Lo siento.
Kaylie...
Kaylie...
seriously?
¿En serio?
Oh, God.
Joder.
This was a terrible idea.
Ha sido una mala idea.
Twenty minutes ago, you were so pumped up about this.
Hace 20 minutos te hacía ilusión.
Well, I don't know what I was saying. I was mad.
No sabía qué decía. Estaba enfadada.
God. Can you please not make this about you?
Dios. ¿Puedes no centrar esto en ti?
Oh, I'm not making this about me. I just don't want to be here anymore.
¡No lo centro en mí! Es que no quiero seguir aquí.
I want the bus to pull over right now so we can get off.
Quiero que pare el autobús y bajar.
- Right on cue. - Wait, what is happening?
- Justo a tiempo. - ¿Qué es esto?
People are getting ready. We're getting close to Ángel.
Se están preparando.
You can feel the vibrations.
Siente las vibraciones.
What? No.
¿Qué? No.
Kaylie.
Kaylie.
This is not happening. Please make it stop. Please.
Esto no está pasando. Haz que pare. Por favor.
I mean, can you believe those two? It's crazy. They just left?
¿Te lo puedes creer? Es de locos. Acaban de irse.
Yeah! I know, right?
Ya, qué cosas.
So selfish.
Qué egoístas.
Okay. What do we think?
Vale. ¿Qué te parece?
So, what's up with this dude? What makes him so...
¿Qué tiene ese tío? ¿Qué hace que…
I dunno, worth all the trouble? You know?
valga tanto la pena?
I don't know. He's like the opposite of a flaky LA dude.
No sé. Es lo contrario a un tío de Los Ángeles.
He has a job. He has a house. He's not friends with people who DJ.
Tiene trabajo. Casa. No es amigo de gente que pincha.
Oh. So, it's a safe bet.
Es una apuesta segura.
No-No-No. I'm obviously not describing him right. Um...
No. No lo estoy describiendo bien.
He's very hot.
Está muy bueno.
Oh, you're done. So, he's hot and safe. That's good.
Ah, es eso. Está bueno y te da seguridad.
That's not it.
No es solo eso.
I mean, very first time we were together... Sorry, fucking...
La primera vez que estuvimos juntos, follando,
He lit candles, he had, like, rose petals going.
puso velas, pétalos de rosa...
He didn't even get imaginative.
Ni se lo curró.
It's called being romantic, Sean. Read any book or watch any movie.
Se llama ser romántico, Sean. Lee un libro o mira una película.
Candles and flowers.
Velas y flores.
Wow. Sounds like a Bachelorette episode.
Caray. Parece un programa de citas.
What do you know about romance, anyway?
¿Qué sabes tú del amor?
And what happened? You "automatic-out" her?
¿Y qué pasó? ¿Usaste la salida automática?
No, she, she died.
No, murió.
Oh, my God.
Madre mía.
- I'm so sorry. - I'm good.
- Perdona. - Tranqui.
I'm moving forward. It's been two years. I'm good.
No es nada. Han pasado dos años. Estoy bien.
Wait. So, you're just now starting to date again.
Estás empezando a quedar ahora.
Please, tell me I wasn't your first date.
Dime que no fui tu primera cita.
And my last.
Y la última.
- No. - Yeah. That shit's too complicated.
- No. - Sí. Demasiado complicado.
- Don't go there, okay? - Yeah.
- No vayas por ahí. - Sí.
You were totally right. I was in a really bad place that night.
Tenías razón. No actué bien esa noche.
No, this is not your fault. This is on me. You know what? I...
No es culpa tuya. Es culpa mía. ¿Sabes qué?
I was trying to get back out there, right? Maybe I moved a little bit too fast.
Intentaba volver al ruedo. Quizá fui demasiado rápido.
I forced myself to do my thing, and then...
Me forcé a hacerlo y...
you came along, and it just got a little bit too real for me.
llegaste tú y vi que era algo serio.
- So... - Yes. Exactly.
- Así que... - Exacto.
I'm too real too much of the time.
Soy demasiado real.
Even my e-mail to Jared is too real.
Hasta el correo a Jared fue real.
It's too early in our story to be that real.
Es demasiado pronto para ser tan real.
You're always later in your story than you think.
Mejor pronto que tarde.
Come on.
Venga.
Seriously, so sorry.
En serio, lo siento mucho.
So, do you wanna, like,
¿Quieres...
hang out a little more? Maybe wait with me?
echar el rato? ¿Esperar conmigo?
- I don't know these streets. - You don't know them?
- No conozco estas calles. - ¿No?
- I don't know them, no. - Not familiar with these blocks.
- No. - No conozco esta zona.
I mean, you don't have to, but... It would be... Oh, one second.
No hace falta, pero... Un segundo.
- Hello. - Hey, it's me.
- ¿Diga? - Hola, soy yo.
Hi, Jared.
Hola, Jared.
- Is that Jarard? - I have a surprise for you.
- ¿Es Jarard? - Tengo una sorpresa.
I'm coming to take you home.
¡Voy a llevarte a casa!
Stop it. I'm coming home today. You don't have to do that.
Vuelvo hoy. No tienes por qué hacerlo.
No, babe. I'm already here.
No, cariño. Ya estoy aquí.
- Wait, you're what? - Yeah. I just landed in Cabo.
- ¿Qué? - Acabo de aterrizar en Cabo.
- I'm in the airport. - That's sweet.
Estoy en el aeropuerto.
You didn't have to...
No tenías...
You didn't have to come all the way to Cabo for me.
que venir a Cabo por mí.
- What? - Is that him there?
- ¿Qué? - ¿Es él?
- Where? - There.
- Ahí.
Who's that?
¿Quién es?
Oh, my God! Jared.
¡Madre mía! Jared.
What? Are you okay?
¿Estás bien?
Oh, my God.
Madre mía.
Jared. I am so freaking excited to be in Mexico.
Jared. Me hace mucha ilusión estar en México.
Great. I guess just wait where you are. They're taking me to the airport.
Genial. Espera donde estés. Me llevan al aeropuerto.
What about your computer and all your stuff?
¿Y tu ordenador y todo eso?
No. The manager at the hotel,
No. El encargado del hotel envió todas mis maletas. Buen tío.
We gotta come back here now that I got the hookup.
Acaba de llegar mi transporte.
Honey, you have to take it easy.
Tienes que relajarte.
Okay? Don't even go near that computer.
¿Vale? No te acerques a ese ordenador.
No, I couldn't if I wanted to. They've got our bags in another van.
No puedo. Las maletas están en otra furgoneta.
Oh, I gotta give the phone back.
Tengo que dejar el teléfono.
I'll get there as soon as I can,
Llegaré pronto,
but we got a bunch of people we gotta drop off first,
pero hay que llevar a un montón de gente.
- so it might be a few hours, okay? Bye. - Okay.
- Así que tardaré. ¿Vale? Adiós. - Vale.
Sorry, just making travel arrangements with my girlfriend.
Lo siento, me organizaba con mi novia.
Just called me his girlfriend.
Me ha llamado "novia".
He just called me his girlfriend! Did you hear that?
Ha dicho que soy tu novia. ¿Has oído eso?
- Shut up, now this is a big deal for you. - It is.
- Esto es increíble. - Sí.
This means so much.
Mucho.
Now, you get to tell the kids
Podrás contarle a tus hijos
how Mommy stalked Daddy all the way to Mexico like a bounty hunter.
que acosaste a papá en México como una cazarrecompensas.
I have to ask you something. Please say yes.
Tengo que preguntarte algo. Di que sí.
Will you take me to the airport to see him? Please?
¿Me llevas al aeropuerto? ¿Por favor?
I mean, I'm already invested, so...
Ya me he metido en esto...
Oh, my God!
¡Qué fuerte!
God, this is so good. What is in this tea?
Qué bueno está esto. ¿Qué es?
Ah, I think that's just regular green tea.
Es un té verde normal.
I don't think so. I mean, it's got a spice to it.
No creo. Es algo especiado.
- It's so good. - Oh, lookee here...
- Está muy rico. - Mira...
"Remove your inner thorn." Mm. That sounds painful.
"Quítate la espina". Eso tiene que doler.
I know, Brookie. I used to think it was bullshit too,
Yo también pensaba que eran tonterías,
then I actually read the book, and it spoke to me.
pero leí el  libro y me dijo algo.
Oh, really? What did it say to you?
¿En serio? ¿Qué te dijo?
It said "Be a tree. Find your roots."
"Sé un árbol. Encuentra tus raíces".
Really? It's fascinating.
¿De verdad? Es fascinante.
Okay.
Vale.
Thanks. It's delicious.
Gracias. Está muy rico.
Oh, my God. It's so hot here, I wanna die.
Joder, me muero de calor.
- Look at this. Look how big this jungle... - Hola, ladies.
- Mira esto. Mira qué jungla... - Hola.
Hi.
Hola.
Welcome to the heart sanctuary.
Bienvenidas al santuario.
- Let's go. - Since when is she a chick?
- Vamos. - ¿Era una tía?
I never said Ángel was a man.
No dije que fuera un hombre.
Well, forgive me for assuming
Perdona por pensar
that a scam artist, hippie, sociopath wouldn't be a woman.
que un estafador sociópata no era una mujer.
Welcome. I'm Ángel de la Paz.
Bienvenidas. Soy Ángel de la Paz.
Hi. I'm Brooke de Ketel One.
Hola. Soy Brooke de Smirnoff.
I'm Kaylie. I'm so honored to be here. Thank you.
Soy Kaylie. Es un honor estar aquí. Gracias.
You're so beautiful and amazing,
Eres preciosa e increíble,
and I just wanna say namaste.
y solo quiero decir namasté.
God bless. Shabbat shalom! Mazel tov.
Dios te bendiga. Shabbat shalom. Mazel tov.
Thank you. I love you.
Muchas gracias. Te quiero.
Oh, actually, just her.
Es solo ella.
I like my healers with an MD and access to Vicodin.
Prefiero que mi médico tenga acceso a la vicodina.
I'm sorry for my friend. I'm-I'm trying to get pregnant.
Discúlpela. Intento quedarme embarazada.
- Have you seen a fertility doctor? - Yes. Seen every doctor in LA,
- ¿Ha visto a un médico? - A todos los médicos de la ciudad
and nothing has worked.
y no ha funcionado nada.
I'm sorry. This must be very painful.
Lo siento. Debe de ser muy doloroso.
Thank you.
Gracias.
There's nothing I can do for you.
No puedo hacer nada.
What? No, I'm in Mexico.
¿Qué? No, estoy en México.
I read all the things about all the women who come visit you.
He leído a mujeres que vienen a visitarte.
I can't help you get pregnant, but I think you'll be a great mother.
No puedo ayudarte a quedarte embarazada, pero serás una gran madre.
Stay open, and life will bring you someone special to mother.
Sigue así y la vida te traerá a alguien especial.
Okay, you know what? I knew it. This whole thing is a joke.
¿Sabes qué? Lo sabía. Todo esto es una farsa.
Come on. You don't need this. You don't. Let's go.
Venga. No necesitas esto. Vamos.
Not so fast, Ketel One.
Espera, Smirnoff.
Thank you so much for helping out. You're such a buddy.
Gracias por echarme una mano. Eres un amigo.
And listen, I'm here if you ever...
Y estoy aquí si necesitas...
need to talk about your dead wife.
hablar de tu esposa muerta.
Wife. Your deceased spouse...
Esposa. Tu difunta esposa,
who has passed away. What do you call her?
que ha fallecido. ¿Cómo la llamas?
- Rachel. - Rachel, yeah.
- Rachel. - Vale.
- Yep, that's her name. - Makes more sense.
- Sí. - Tiene más sentido.
- I'm so sorry. - No, you're all good. It's okay.
- Lo siento. - No pasa nada.
That's gotta be tough.
Tiene que ser duro.
But, Rachel, she...
Pero, Rachel...
she would've appreciated your directness.
habría apreciado tu franqueza.
- Was she funny? - Oh, yeah.
- ¿Era graciosa? - Ah, sí.
That was our favorite thing to do, was laugh.
Lo que más nos gustaba era reírnos.
And honestly, that's one of the things that I miss most about her,
Una de las cosas que más echo de menos
is having someone just give a little nudge
es tener a alguien a quien decir: "¿Ves a ese capullo?"
Oh, my God, yes. The dinner-party glance.
Madre mía, sí. La mirada de la cena.
- Yes. - When you both clock
Cuando os dais cuenta
something insane is happening,
de que pasa algo raro
and you know you get to talk about it on the drive home.
y sabéis que lo hablaréis de camino.
- That's my favorite. - Yeah, me too.
- Me encanta. - A mí también.
- Right? - Yeah.
- ¿Verdad? - Sí.
Anyway, I-I'm here for you.
Puedes contar conmigo.
- Thank you, I appreciate that, though. - Honestly, I'm a guidance counselor.
- Gracias, te lo agradezco. - La verdad es que soy orientadora.
No shit!
¡No jodas!
I am. Why are you so surprised?
Sí. ¿Por qué te sorprende tanto?
- People pay you to give advice? - Yes.
¿Cobras por dar consejos?
- Wow. - They will when I get a job.
Cuando consiga un trabajo.
That's pretty cool.
Mola bastante.
Wait, why are the vans splitting up?
¿Por qué se separan?
It's decision time, Wes.
Momento decisivo.
Do we follow Jared, or do we follow Jared's stuff?
¿Seguimos a Jared o a sus cosas?
I say we follow Jared...
Mejor a Jared...
- Sean, his stuff is... Go! - Okay!
- ¡A sus cosas! - ¡Vale!
Chill.
Tranqui.
I know you're wondering if this is a good idea, and the answer is:
Te preguntarás si es buena idea y la respuesta es:
- "Please shut up." - Keep it up.
- "Cállate" - Sigue así.
Oh, my God! Learn to drive! Stop!
¡Aprende a conducir! ¡Para!
Jesus.
Joder.
- You okay? - I'm good. We're okay.
- ¿Estás bien? - Sí, todo bien.
It's like the fucking car is giving birth to me.
Es como si el coche me estuviera dando a luz.
Sean, push the car!
¡Empuja el coche!
That's like 2,000 pounds. You crazy?
¡Pero si pesa dos toneladas!
You're doing nothing.
¡No sirve de nada!
Sean, help me flip the car. Come on!
Ayúdame a darle la vuelta al coche. ¡Vamos!
- "Flip the car"? - Yes, people can flip cars
- ¿Cómo? - Sí, la gente puede volcar coches
- in moments of crisis. - This is a crisis?
- en momentos de crisis - ¿Como este?
- Yes, my love life is a crisis right now! - Aye-aye...
Mi vida amorosa es una crisis.
- Come on. On the count of three. - Okay! Okay, okay.
- Venga. A la de tres. - Vale.
- Okay. - One, two, three.
- Uno, dos, tres.
- Fuck! - Fuck.
- ¡Joder! - Joder.
- Fuck you, jeep! Fuck you! - Hey, chill.
- ¡Que te den, coche! - Oye, tranqui.
Fuck you, goat!
¡Que te den, cabra!
- Yeah, that goat is a bitch, dude! - The goat's a bitch?
- Sí, es lo peor. - ¿La cabra?
We have no idea where we are... Why are you laughing?
No sabemos dónde estamos. ¿De qué te ríes?
Is this for real?
¿Va en serio?
- And where the hell are we? - I don't know where we are.
- ¿Dónde coño estamos? - No lo sé.
- We'll figure it out. Hey. - Oh, my God.
- Lo averiguaremos. - Madre mía.
Hey, look at me.
Oye, mírame.
We're gonna be fine.
Estaremos bien.
We walk.
Caminaremos.
Come on.
Venga ya.
That goat is still looking at you, by the way.
La cabra sigue mirándote.
Breathe in. Breathe out.
Inspira. Expira.
Feel the softness of the air as it flows through your bodily vessel.
Siente el aire fluyendo por todo tu cuerpo.
The air is nurturing your flower, and it's opening...
El aire alimenta tu flor y se abre...
Feel the flower open, Brooke.
Siente cómo se abre.
Feel your roots going deep into the earth,
Siente cómo tus raíces se adentran
grounding you.
en la tierra.
You can just cut the crap, right now.
Corta el rollo ya.
Just drop the act 'cause I know you're just a Goop wannabe.
Deja de fingir. Eres una Gwyneth Paltrow de pacotilla.
And I also think you were kind of an asshole
Y fuiste una idiota
to my very sweet, sensitive friend out there.
con mi dulce y sensible amiga.
Well, I'm honest. Don't you fancy yourself a truth-teller?
Soy sincera. ¿No te gusta la sinceridad?
Yeah, I guess you could say that,
Sí, supongo que se podría decir eso,
but see, I don't charge people for my magical pearls of wisdom.
pero no cobro a la gente por mis perlas mágicas de sabiduría.
Your heart is sad.
Estás triste.
Unbroken eye contact is a particular kind of torture.
El contacto visual ininterrumpido es un tipo de tortura.
But you would put a bunch of fire... Never mind.
Pero podrías hacer un fuego. Da igual.
- For a million dollars, I would. - One million?
Por un millón de dólares.
- Fire ants in my butt? - What?
¿Hormigas en el culo?
- That's a lot of money. - Oh, my goodness.
- Es mucho dinero. - Madre mía.
Okay, this is gonna sound strange,
Esto va a sonar raro,
- very strange, but... - Okay.
- pero que muy raro. - Vale.
Kicking it with you has kind of been the best part of my trip.
Caminar contigo ha sido lo mejor de mi viaje.
- What? - Yeah.
- ¿Qué? - Sí.
- We were just in a car accident. - I get it.
- Hemos tenido un accidente. - Ya.
I get it. You definitely come with some nonsense.
Hay cosas de ti que no entiendo.
Look, meaning, you got some layers.
Quiero decir que tienes capas.
- Oh no, that's fair. Yeah. - Right.
- Ya, lo entiendo. - Vale.
You see, that's why I think you'd make a great guidance counselor.
Por eso creo que serías una buena orientadora.
What I'm saying is, you have a very youthful soul, you know?
Lo que digo es que tienes un alma muy juvenil.
Wanna hear something crazy? I used to be in corporate finance.
¿Sabes qué? Trabajaba en finanzas corporativas.
- That's very weird. - Yeah.
Eso sí que es raro.
Very weird fit.
Muy raro.
Not for me. But eventually, I followed my passion, and...
No para mí. Pero al final, seguí mi pasión,
that's not really working out either.
y tampoco me va bien.
I don't know what to do.
No sé qué hacer.
Come on, now, Wes,
Vamos, Wes,
eventually you'll find that one place that appreciates you for you.
encontrarás un lugar que te aprecie por cómo eres.
Yeah, if that place even exists.
Sí, si ese lugar existe.
The world will catch up to you.
Ya llegará tu momento.
Wait, wait, wait.
Espera.
Oh, my God. Is that the van?
¿Esa es la furgoneta?
That van has Jared's bag in it.
Ahí está la bolsa de Jared.
He's playing in a band?
¿Toca en una banda?
What is happening?
¿Qué está pasando?
It's like a Mexican sweet 16, only she's 15.
Como cuando las mexicanas cumplen 16.
It's a combination of the words, "quince," meaning "15,"
Una combinación de las palabras "quince"...
you understand? And "años," meaning "years."
Y "años", que significa...
I know what a quinceañera is, Sean.
Sé lo que es, Sean.
- You know what that is? - Why's he at the quinceañera?
- Ah, ya lo sabes. - ¿Qué hace ahí?
- He's supposed to be at the airport. - I don't know, he's hopping out of a cake.
- ¿No está en el aeropuerto? - Sale de una tarta.
I do not know this man.
No lo conozco.
Dude, come on. We gotta find out what the driver's doing here.
Venga. Hay que averiguar qué hace ahí.
I wonder if they got tacos in there.
Me pregunto si tendrán tacos.
That's really not important right now.
Eso ahora no importa.
It's the most important thing I can think of.
No hay nada más importante.
Another hot pile of horseshit.
Otro montón de mierda.
A little background. Kaylie.
Os cuento. Me llamo Kaylie.
Came here from Los Angeles. My dreams were crushed today,
Vengo de Los Ángeles y me han roto la ilusión,
so I'm feeling a little tender.
así que estoy sensible.
I'm gonna be hosting a class by the aqueduct tomorrow morning called:
Mañana daré una clase junto al acueducto llamada:
"Losers never win, you can eat shit all day,
"Los perdedores nunca ganan, podrás comer mierda todo el día
and it's not ever gonna taste any better."
pero el sabor no mejorará".
Fuck you. Fuck you.
Que os den.
You can just stop staring at me right now. Please stop.
Deja de mirarme ahora mismo. Por favor, para.
Stop smiling.
No sonrías.
You have a beautiful soul. Let it out.
Tienes un alma hermosa. Suéltalo.
- I don't know what's happening. - You're feeling your feelings, Brooke.
- No sé qué pasa. - Son tus sentimientos, Brooke.
Our hearts are talking through my hand.
Hablan nuestros corazones.
Oh, my God.
Madre mía.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
Dios mío, lo siento.
I'm so sorry, I can't...
Lo siento, no puedo...
You're crying because your marriage is over.
Tu matrimonio ha terminado.
No, you just saw the indentation where my wedding ring used to be.
No, me has visto la marca del anillo.
That doesn't mean that my marriage is over.
Pero no ha terminado.
It is.
Sí.
You know it already, but you haven't let yourself feel it.
Ya lo sabes, pero no te dejas sentirlo.
Pain and sadness, it's uncomfortable for you.
El dolor y la tristeza te incomodan.
- Yeah. - Anger feels safer.
La ira es más segura.
- It does. - Beware, beautiful Brooke,
- Sí. - Cuidado, preciosa Brooke,
that rage fuels you now, but it will destroy you,
esa rabia te alimenta, pero te destruirá
and it would destroy the life of your child.
y destruirá la vida de tu hijo.
- You love him so much, it's so... - I love my son.
- Le quieres tanto que es… - Quiero a mi hijo.
But you have to love yourself first.
Pero tienes que liberarte.
- You have to love your inner child. - I have to love myself.
- Ama a tu niña interior. - Quererme.
Love baby Brooke. Do you know where she is right now?
Me encanta, Brooke. ¿Sabes dónde está ahora?
God, baby Brooke. I have to love her. Where is she?
Tengo que quererla. ¿Dónde está?
You need to take care of her.
Tienes que cuidarla.
She wants an ice-cream cone.
Quiere un cono de helado.
She wants to run outside in a field of daisies.
Quiere correr en un campo de margaritas.
And I think baby Brooke really wants to get fucked.
Y creo que Brooke quiere que se la follen.
Oh, my God.
Madre mía.
Good news. I just spoke to Carlotta, the owner of the hacienda.
He hablado con Carlotta, la dueña de la hacienda.
- It's all taken care of. - It is?
- Ya está todo arreglado. - ¿Sí?
She hooked it up. So, her brother, the driver,
Su hermano, el conductor,
he's gonna take us to the airport when he's done.
nos llevará al aeropuerto cuando acabe.
- Thank you. - And in a couple of hours,
- Gracias. - En un par de horas
you get to be Mrs. Jared What-the-fuck.
serás la señora Jared no sé qué.
Sterling. Cannot wait.
Sterling. Qué ganas.
- Oh, it's okay, señor. We don't need... - No, we're good.
- Tranquilo, señor. - Estamos bien.
- Sean, we're not guests here. - Oh, speak for yourself.
- Sean, no estamos invitados. - Habla por ti.
Carlotta said to eat. In fact, your non-eating is offending her.
Carlotta dijo que comiéramos. De hecho, que no comas la ofende.
- Okay, fine. - You ain't gotta be that mad.
No hace falta que te enfades.
- Okay. - Take a bite.
- Vale. - Dale un mordisco.
- Oh, my God. - It's good, right?
Está rico, ¿eh?
- It's really good. What is that? - It's crickets.
- Está muy bueno. ¿Qué es eso? - Son grillos.
- What? - Yeah.
- ¿Qué? - Sí.
- Crickets on the top. - Why would you let me eat that?
- Grillos. - ¿Por qué me haces esto?
- The chapulines? - Oh, God. I'm gonna kill you.
- ¿Los chapulines? - Te mato.
Wow. You know, such a classy date.
Vaya. Una cita con clase.
Oh, like you were such a better date.
Como si tú fueras mejor.
Well, excuse me.
Perdóname.
Why don't you show me how it's done, Coach?
Enséñame cómo se hace.
You want me to show you how to be on a date?
¿Te enseño a tener una cita?
- I gotta get back out there. - I will train you.
Te entrenaré.
- Oh, you're gonna train me? Okay. - Ah, huh.
¿Vas a entrenarme? Vale.
- Wesley Darya. - Sean McGuire. Nice to meet you.
- Wesley Darya. - Sean McGuire. Encantado.
Nice to meet you, Sean.
Encantada, Sean.
Why are we shaking for so long?
¿Por qué dura tanto el saludo?
I don't know. It's your training, Coach.
No sé. Tú eres la entrenadora.
So, what do you do? I just realized I don't even know.
No me has dicho a qué te dedicas.
Oh, architect.
Soy arquitecto.
- Architect? Oh, my God. That's awesome. - Yeah. Thank you.
- ¿Arquitecto? Caray, qué guay. - Sí. Gracias.
I love... buildings.
Me encantan... los edificios.
Me too.
A mí también.
So, what are you working on now?
¿Con qué estás ahora?
Nothing.
Con nada.
Oh, just taking a break?
Te tomas un descanso.
I guess you could say that. I...
Se podría decir eso...
Well, ever since Rachel died,
Cuando Rachel murió,
I have taken a leave of absence, and I just haven't gone back.
pedí un permiso y todavía no he vuelto.
- Yeah. - Since then?
¿Desde entonces?
Yeah, it's been a while.
Sí, hace un tiempo ya.
I'm so sorry.
Lo siento.
That's gotta be really hard.
Tiene que ser duro.
Yeah. But you know...
Sí. Pero...
gotta get back out there. At least, that's what my friends say.
Hay que volver. Al menos, eso dicen mis amigos.
They're all worried about me, so that's why I'm here.
Sé preocupan, por eso estoy aquí.
What do you think?
¿Y tú qué crees?
I think...
Creo...
I think I'm doing the best I can.
que lo hago lo mejor que puedo.
Hey, do you wanna dance?
Oye, ¿quieres bailar?
I am not a dancer. I should start with that.
No soy muy de bailar, lo confieso.
- Okay. - But I would love to dance with you.
Pero me encantaría bailar contigo.
- Oh, here we go. - Let's go.
- Allá vamos. - Vamos.
- Goodness. Okay. - Over here.
- Madre mía. Vale. - Aquí.
Oh, boy.
Vaya.
What is that?
¿Qué es eso?
Come on.
Venga.
Yes, Sean!
Sí, Sean.
How are you so good?
¿Cómo se te da tan bien?
Can't believe you slept with my shaman.
¡Te has acostado con mi chamán!
Oh, my God. Everything is so clear to me now.
Madre mía. Ahora lo veo todo claro.
I'm gonna leave Dave.
Dejo a Dave.
- I never liked him for you. - What?
- Nunca me gustó para ti. - ¿Cómo?
Yeah. He couldn't keep up with you, and so he resented you for it
No podía seguirte el ritmo. Eso le molestaba
and tried to drag you down.
y te arrastraba.
But that's not what the person you're with is supposed to do.
Pero no es con quien debes estar.
- They're supposed to build you up. - Why did you never say anything?
- Él no te entendía. - ¿Y no me lo habías dicho?
Because it's your thing to discover.
Porque tenías que descubrirlo tú.
Thank you.
Gracias.
You're welcome.
De nada.
I'm really sorry about today.
Siento mucho lo de hoy.
And I know you don't like hearing this, but there are other ways.
Ya, pero sabes que hay otras formas.
I know adoption takes forever, but...
La adopción tarda mucho pero...
Well, not if you wanna adopt an older kid. The foster care system can't place them.
No si adoptas a un niño mayor. Cuesta mucho encontrarles familia.
Tad's been talking about it.
Tad lo planteó.
- Oh, yeah? - I just can't believe
- ¿Sí? - No puedo creer
how fucking frustrating it is.
lo frustrante que es.
Why does it come so easily for everyone else?
Para los demás es muy fácil.
I'm just so sick of my body not working. I wanna fix it.
Estoy harta de que mi cuerpo no funcione.
And what if you can't fix it?
¿Y si no puedes arreglarlo?
Don't you still deserve to be happy?
¿No te mereces ser feliz?
Kinda feels weird talking about all this stuff without Wesley here.
Es un poco raro hablar de esto sin Wesley.
Yeah, well, if Wesley were here, we wouldn't be talking about our stuff.
Si estuviera aquí, no estaríamos hablando de nuestras cosas.
- God, that's sad. - But true.
- Ya, qué triste. - Pero cierto.
Yep. It's bad.
Sí. Es grave.
His dad is dead. Isn't that so sad?
Su padre está muerto. ¿No es triste?
So, I just wanna be clear. You sent this to him?
Que me quede claro, ¿le enviaste esto?
- Yes, I sent it. - On purpose?
- Sí. - ¿A propósito?
With my friends. Yeah, very much on purpose.
Con mis amigas. Muy a propósito.
Very crazy.
Muy loco.
- Yeah, it's very crazy. - Yeah.
- Una locura. - Sí.
- You wanna know what I would do? - Sure.
- ¿Sabes qué haría yo? - ¿Qué?
You should let him read it.
Deja que lo lea.
- What? No. - I'd let him read it.
- No. - Yo le dejaría.
- I'm not letting him read it. - Yes!
- No lo leerá.. - ¡Sí!
Look, he's gotta like all sides of you.
Tiene que gustarle todo.
You don't wanna pop up with a little bit of crazy one day,
Un día te saldrá la locura por algún lado
and then, surprise! He's out.
y él se irá.
I know you think this guy doesn't know me very well,
Crees que este tío no me conoce,
but just so you know, he knows...
pero para que lo sepas,
- he knows my essence. - Oh, he knows your essence?
- conoce mi esencia. - ¿Tu esencia?
Cool, cool, cool. What is his favorite thing about you?
Está bien. ¿Qué es lo que más le gusta de ti?
So many things.
Muchas cosas.
At some point, I'm sure he said, "Know what I love about you? You're..."
Seguro que dice: "¿Sabes lo que me gusta de ti?"
He has mentioned that he...
Ha mencionado que...
likes that I'm the last...
le gusta que sea la única... chica normal en Los Ángeles.
Look, Wes. You are a lot of things, but normal definitely is not one of them.
Mira, Wes. Eres un montón de cosas, pero la normalidad no es tu fuerte.
- Normal's not one of them. - No.
- Normal no soy. - No.
That's very accurate.
Es cierto.
If you ask me, maybe you should be with someone who loves that about you.
Yo creo que deberías estar con alguien a quien le guste eso de ti.
I don't even know if I love that about me.
No sé ni si me gusta a mí.
All right.
Vale.
Oh, my God. Wait, we're here.
Un momento... Ya hemos llegado.
Look, um, e-mail me.
Mira, envíame un correo.
Call me, text me, whatever you wanna do. I wanna know how this all plays out.
Llámame o escríbeme. Quiero saber cómo termina esto.
Thanks for being there.
Gracias por estar ahí.
Yeah. This was fun.
Sí. Ha sido divertido.
I had so much fun with you.
Me he divertido mucho.
- I had a lot of fun. - Right?
Lo he pasado muy bien.
- Today was a fantastic day. - Thank you.
- Ha sido un día fantástico. - Gracias.
You took me on a journey. I'm not that adventurous.
Me has llevado de viaje. No suelo hacerlo.
Well, I am a little manic, so...
Es que estoy un poco loca.
I can appreciate that.
Te lo agradezco.
Thanks.
Gracias.
Okay.
Vale.
Okay.
Vale.
- Okay, bye. - Right, yeah.
- Vale, adiós. - Sí.
Right, right, right, right...
Vale.
You take it easy.
Con calma.
- Oh, my God. Jared! - Oh, hey.
- Madre mía. ¡Jared! - Hola.
- Hi! Are you okay? - You made it. Hi!
- ¿Estás bien? - Has podido venir.
Oh, God. You scared me. Oh, he's fine.
Ay, me has asustado. Está bien.
- Hey.
- Hola.
I missed you.
Te extrañaba.
Finally. Thank you. Gracias.
Por fin. Gracias.
Thank you.
Gracias.
- I'll take you to the gate myself, okay? - No, I can take him to the gate.
- Te llevaré a la puerta. - No, puedo llevarlo yo.
- Please, take care of him. He's weak. - I will. He's mine.
- Cuide de él. Está débil. - Sí. Es mío.
She's very attached to you. Let's get you to LA, huh?
Está muy unida a ti. Volvamos a casa.
Are you excited?
¿Tienes ganas?
Back to civilization...
De vuelta a la civilización.
- Back to civilization. Yes. - And air conditioning.
- Sí. - Y al aire acondicionado.
And 2,000 e-mails. Actually,
Y 2.000 correos.
do you think my phone has any charge in it?
¿Me quedará batería?
No, I don't think it's charged.
No creo que esté cargado.
- You shouldn't even be carrying stuff. - Just a little...
- Pero no lleves peso. - Solo un...
No, I'm fine...
No, estoy bien...
You should not be doing things
No deberías hacer cosas
- like holding laptops. - Hey, Wes, there you are.
- como llevar un portátil. - Hola.
- Look who made it to the airport. - Hello...
- Mira quién ha llegado. - Hola...
ladies.
chicas.
I just got here from Los Angeles. This is Jared.
Acabo de llegar de Los Ángeles. Este es Jared.
- Hi. - Jared, these are my...
- Hola. - Jared, estas son...
Some acquaintances.
mis conocidas.
Hey, Jared.
Hola, Jared.
- Jared got really hurt recently. - Yeah, this is not the usual getup.
- Se ha hecho mucho daño. - Sí, esta no es mi ropa habitual.
- Oh, you're in great hands. - So sweet. She's so selfless.
- Estás en buenas manos. - Es que es tan amable.
- Florence Nightingale. - Yeah.
- Una enfermera de primera. - Sí.
- So great to see you guys. Okay. - So nice to meet you.
- Me alegro de veros. - Un placer.
- We can't wait to run into you again... - Totes. Don't wanna end up like me.
Qué ganas de volvernos a encontrar.
- Soon. - Literally don't remember
Ni me acuerdo
- those girls. - Or not soon.
de esas chicas.
Why don't we get you another Percocet so you could pass out?
¿Por qué no te tomas otro calmante y duermes un poco?
No, I don't wanna get too wrecked.
No quiero pasarme con eso.
The doctors wouldn't prescribe it unless it was safe for you to...
Los médicos no lo recetarían si no fuera seguro.
- Okay, well... - take as much as you want.
Toma lo que quieras.
- There you go. - Thank you.
- Eso es. - Gracias.
Good night.
Buenas noches.
Got it?
¿Todo bien?
Oh, long time no see.
¡Cuánto tiempo!
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hola.
- Have a safe flight. - You too.
- Pasad un buen vuelo. - Igualmente.
Well, they sure pop up everywhere.
Están hasta en la sopa.
- Hey. - Yeah?
- Oye. - Dime.
Babe, look over there.
Cariño, mira ahí.
That guy.
Ese tío.
What is he doing? That's crazy.
¿Qué hace? Qué ida de olla.
- I don't know. It's just feet. - "It's just feet"?
- No sé. Solo son pies. - ¿"Solo pies"?
He should be banned from the plane.
Deberían expulsarlo.
- Don't make a big deal out of it. - Disgusting.
- No le des más vueltas. - Qué asco.
Okay?
¿Vale?
What?
¿Qué?
Jared?
¿Jared?
Jared.
Jared.
Sorry. Are you awake?
Perdona. ¿Estás despierto?
I... What? Yes.
¿Qué? Sí.
I'm really...
Me...
really worried about...
preocupa mucho...
showing this to you, but I want you to know that, um...
enseñarte esto, pero la verdad... es que escribí un correo...
to you during those five days that you went missing
durante esos cinco días que desapareciste
where I... just, a little bit, lost my mind...
en el que se me fue un poco la cabeza
and I just need to show you that e-mail.
y tengo que enseñártelo.
Well, I don't know how you got into my phone, but...
No sé cómo has desbloqueado el móvil...
- Yeah, I just scanned your face. - That's for...
- Ya, he escaneado tu cara. - Es...
Have you started yet?
¿Has empezado ya?
Oh, yeah.
Sí, sí.
- I know... - Wow, this is just mean.
- Lo sé. - Qué cruel...
I know, I'm so sorry.
Lo sé, lo siento.
If we're gonna do this, you need to know
Si seguimos, tienes que conocer
me at my best and at my worst,
lo bueno y lo malo de mí.
which...
Y esta...
this e-mail is my worst.
es mi peor cara.
I know.
Lo sé.
This was me just one night
Era yo una noche después
after you had disappeared for five days, and...
de que desaparecieras durante 5 días...
- This is hurtful. - I want us to be real.
- Eso duele. - Quiero que seamos sinceros.
You know, like, both let our mustaches grow out.
Los dos nos podemos dejar bigote.
"Our mustaches"?
¿"Bigotes"?
I have a mustache. This is the thing I'm talking about.
Tengo bigote. Eso es lo que digo.
Like, you don't know that. But you should know,
No lo sabes. Pero deberías saber
if I don't take care of it, I, too, can grow a mustache.
que si no me depilo, yo también puedo tener bigote.
That's not... The point is, the Band-Aid's been ripped off now,
La cuestión es... que quiero quitarme la careta
and I just wanna be real with you.
y quiero ser de verdad.
The good and the bad.
Lo bueno y lo malo.
We don't have to pretend. We don't have to pretend to be perfect.
No tenemos que fingir que somos perfectos.
You've just been pretending to be somebody else?
¿Has fingido ser otra persona?
Don't you wanna just get to know the real me?
¿No quieres conocer el verdadero yo?
No.
No.
I want that girl.
Quiero aquella chica.
This girl's... crazy.
Esta está... loca.
Jared, don't do this. Come on.
Jared, no hagas esto. Vamos.
- Excuse me. - Wait.
- Disculpe. - Espera.
- Miss? - What are you doing?
- ¿Señorita? - ¿Qué haces?
Is there another seat open that...
¿Hay algún asiento libre...
this stranger could sit in?
en el que pueda sentarse?
Maybe surrounded by a bunch of other liars?
¿Con otros mentirosos tal vez?
No. You know what? Forget it. I'll...
No. ¿Sabes qué? Olvídalo. Yo…
Come on, don't embarrass me. I'll go.
No me humilles. Me voy.
I'm really sorry, okay? I'm sorry about everything.
Lo siento mucho, ¿vale? Lo siento por todo.
Kaylie? Brooke?
¿Kaylie? ¿Brooke?
Kaylie.
Kaylie.
I'm really sorry.
Lo siento mucho.
Your attention, please. Baggage from flight 746
Atención, por favor. El equipaje del vuelo 746
can be retrieved at carousel B.
se recoge en la cinta B.
Sweetie, it's gonna be okay.
Cariño, todo irá bien.
This fucking trip. What a mistake.
Este puto viaje... Qué error.
Yeah, it sucked.
Pues sí.
I mean, honestly, Jared has a ridiculous notion
Sinceramente, Jared tiene una noción ridícula
of what women should be. I'm not like a trophy pet.
de las las mujeres. No soy una novia trofeo.
It must be so hard to feel unappreciated.
Debe de ser muy duro que no te aprecien.
What are you... Is that a dig?
¿Te metes conmigo?
- What are you doing right now? I'm... - Wes...
- ¿Qué haces ahora? - Wes...
we're just feeling a little neglected, that's all.
nos sentimos un poco abandonadas, eso es todo.
- Hmm. - Look, I'm sorry that I've been...
Siento haberme...
a little wrapped up in Jared.
obsesionado un poco con Jared.
"A little"?
¿Un poco?
Did she just say "a little"?
¿Ha dicho "un poco"?
Wes, you've been obsessed to the point of blindness.
Wes, la obsesión te ha cegado.
- I know. - Wesley, I'm getting a divorce,
- Lo sé. - Wesley, me voy a divorciar
and Kaylie is adopting a baby.
y Kaylie va a adoptar un bebé.
What? When did this happen?
¿Qué? ¿Cuándo habéis decidido eso?
We were apart for six hours.
Estuvimos separadas seis horas.
That's all the time that it took because you weren't there,
Era el tiempo que necesitábamos sin ti
sucking up all of the energy in the room, and we had time to think.
absorbiendo toda la energía. Tuvimos tiempo para pensar.
Good for you.
Pues me alegro.
You figured your shit out with superhuman speed.
Habéis solucionado vuestros problemas superrápido.
I'm sorry I'm not as together as you are.
Siento no haber estado tan cerca.
Wes, when you say things like that,
Wes, cuando dices cosas así,
it sounds like you don't take our problems seriously.
parece que no te preocupen nuestros problemas.
Kay, of course I take them seriously.
Kay, claro que me preocupan.
You think your problems are worse.
Crees que los tuyos son peores.
They are worse.
Es que lo son.
I am failing on every level.
Estoy fracasando en todo.
And you are the reason why.
Y tú eres la razón.
You think I don't know that?
¿Creéis que no lo sé?
I live it every day, okay?
Lo vivo todos los días, ¿vale?
I am alone. I have no one.
Estoy sola. No tengo a nadie.
- How can you say that? - Because it's true!
- ¿Cómo puedes decir eso? - ¡Es verdad!
You have two best friends who love you unconditionally.
Tienes dos mejores amigas que te quieren incondicionalmente.
We just flew to fucking Mexico
Hemos viajado a México
to make your world work.
solo por ti.
How is that not enough for you?
¿No es suficiente para ti?
Because it just isn't.
No lo es.
Oh, my God.
Madre mía...
I can't.
No puedo.
- Guys, where... - That's it, Wesley.
- Chicas... - Se acabó.
- Oh, come on. - We need a break.
Queremos descansar.
- Fine, I'm sorry. - We're done.
- Lo siento. - Se acabó.
Don't leave. How am I supposed to get home?
No os vayáis. ¿Cómo vuelvo a casa?
You guys, all I have are pesos!
Chicas, solo tengo pesos.
Wesley, hi. This is Doug Evans from Atwater Village Charter School.
Hola. Soy Doug Evans, del Colegio Atwater Village Charter.
If you could please give me a call back. Thanks.
Si puedes, llámame. Gracias.
We were just a group of parents that were unhappy with
Éramos un grupo de padres que no estaban contentos
how our school was being run.
con algunas cosas.
So here we are, just trying to do it better ourselves.
Así que, nada, intentamos hacerlo mejor.
That is so cool that you're trying something new.
Qué guay que intentéis algo nuevo.
Really. Oh, I checked out the seventh-grade curriculum,
En serio. He visto en plan de estudios de séptimo
and I had some thoughts. Um...
y tengo algunas ideas.
I was just thinking... I mean, unless I'm overstepping.
Bueno... tampoco quiero excederme...
No. Not at all. That's why we hired you.
Para nada. Para eso te contratamos.
We want you here for your voice. I'm excited about your ideas.
Queremos oír las ideas que tienes.
- Thank you. - Yeah.
- Gracias. - Sí.
And it looks like you already have guests in your office.
Y parece que ya tienes a alguien en tu despacho.
Eden Williams.
Eden Williams.
Sent her boyfriend a topless pic, and then...
Le envió una foto en topless a su novio
he forwarded it to the entire lacrosse team.
y él la reenvió a sus amigos.
- Hi, Eden. - Hey.
- Hola, Eden. - Hola.
- If you need me to, I can... - I got this.
- Si necesitas... - Nada.
No. Technology mishaps are kinda my thing.
No. Los contratiempos tecnológicos son lo mío.
Thank you so much.
Muchas gracias.
It's okay. Are you okay?
Ya pasó. ¿Estás bien?
It's not a big deal.
No es para tanto.
My friends are just jealous that I have a boyfriend and they don't.
Mis amigas están celosas de que tenga novio.
Do you wanna know something about love? It can be fucked up!
¿Quieres saber algo del amor? ¡Es una mierda!
Don't tell anyone I said "fuck."
No te chives de esto.
Yeah, I followed a dude to Mexico.
Seguí a un tío a México.
I got arrested and electrocuted, and I'm currently not with this person.
Me han detenido y electrocutado, y ni siquiera estoy con esta persona.
But your friends?
Pero tus amigas...
They're the ones who can help keep your head on straight.
Ellas te ayudan a mantener la cabeza alta.
'Cause they know you, they're looking out for you.
Porque te conocen, te cuidan.
Trust me, boyfriends come and go,
Los novios van y vienen,
but if you're lucky enough to have great friends,
pero si tienes buenas amigas...
I would hold on to that.
me quedaría con eso.
What about you?
¿Y tú?
Do you have that?
¿Lo tienes?
Hey, Brooke. It's Wes. Um...
Hola, Brooke. Soy Wes.
I just...
Quería...
I just wanted to call you and tell you I miss you so much. And...
decirte que te echo mucho de menos. Y...
see how you're doing,
quería saber cómo te va,
how you and Dave are doing.
cómo vais Dave y tú.
I don't know if you've been to Kaylie's house recently,
No sé si has estado en casa de Kaylie últimamente,
but I'm in the area if you're around or wanna talk.
pero estoy en la zona si estás cerca o quieres hablar.
I would really love that. I...
Me encantaría...
Brooke, I have to call you back.
Brooke, luego te llamo.
Kevin, come here, buddy.
Kevin, ven aquí, colega.
Kevin.
Kevin.
Oh, my God.
Madre mía.
Kevin!
¡Kevin!
Kevin.
Kevin.
Come here.
Ven aquí.
Come on, buddy. Help me out.
Vamos, colega. Échame una mano.
Hey, Kevin, these are my nice pants.
Estos son mis pantalones buenos.
Kevin! Kevin!
¡Kevin!
Kaylie.
Kaylie.
She's getting her baby.
Ya tiene a su hijo.
Oh, my God.
Qué fuerte.
Kevin, you Nazi dick!
Kevin, nazi de mierda.
- Sweetie, what's... Wesley? - What in the world was that?
- Cariño, ¿es Wesley? - ¿Qué narices ha sido eso?
Kevin?
¿Kevin?
Wesley? Kevin? Let me...
¿Wesley? ¿Kevin? Déjame...
- He's very violent. - Sweetie.
- Es muy violento. - Cielo.
Sorry, I was trying to rescue your cat.
Lo siento, intentaba rescatar a tu gato.
What's going on?
¿Qué pasa?
I know you're mad at me. And you probably don't want me here,
Sé que estáis enfadadas. y no me querréis aquí,
but if I could say something...
pero quiero decir...
As I was chasing after Kevin,
Mientras perseguía a Kevin,
I was thinking, why does this cat keep trying to escape?
pensaba: ¿por qué este gato intenta escapar?
You know, you're the best parents he'll ever have.
Sois los mejores padres que tendrá.
I mean, really, he has a terrible personality
Tiene una personalidad terrible
and literally looks like Hitler,
y es clavado a Hitler,
and you guys feed him,
pero vosotros le alimentáis, le queréis
and you look after him. And then it dawned on me,
y cuidáis de él. Y luego caí en la cuenta
I'm Kevin.
de que soy Kevin.
What? I...
¿Qué?
I'm flawed and I'm complicated
Tengo defectos, soy complicada
and maybe even a little broken,
y algo inestable,
but you guys love me without judgment.
pero me queréis sin juzgarme.
I think I just felt like I was falling behind, and...
Creo que sentía que me estaba quedando atrás
if only I got my dude, I'd be okay. But...
y si tuviera al chico, estaría bien...
- I get that.
Lo entendemos.
I don't need a dude to be okay.
No necesito a ningún tío.
- And that has to do with the two of you. - Yeah.
- Y eso tiene que ver con vosotras dos. - Sí.
And, much like Kevin, I feel like I've taken you for granted.
Y, al igual que Kevin, creo que no he sabido apreciarlo.
- Yeah. - Mm-hmm.
Ya.
So, I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
Sorry?
¿Cómo?
- Was... Did she say, "I'm sorry"? - I couldn't hear.
- ¿Cómo ha dicho? - No he oído.
I'm so sorry. I'm...
Lo siento mucho...
begging you to forgive me.
Perdonadme, por favor.
And I know that was a lot.
Y sé que fue muy duro.
Ma'am, you must be so lost.
Debe de estar tan perdida...
Please know that Kaylie and Tad
Que sepa que Kaylie y Tad
are gonna take such good care of your baby.
van a cuidar mucho de su bebé.
Hey, Wesley, this is Noelle Grey from Coldwell Banker.
Wesley, ella es Noelle Grey, de la inmobiliaria.
- Putting the house on the market. - Just selling the house.
- Vamos a vender la casa. - Venden la casa.
I had a completely different narrative in my mind.
Tenía otra historia montada en la cabeza.
Oh, my...
Madre...
Hi. How are you?
¿Cómo estás?
Uh, hey. Um...
Hola.
- You look great. - Thanks. So do you.
- Estás genial. - Tú también.
- What are you doing here? - I was looking at your Instagram.
- ¿Qué haces aquí? - Vi tu Instagram.
You posted where you were.
Publicas la ubicación.
I know I'm probably not supposed to admit that,
Sé que no debería decirlo,
but I'm trying to be honest and own my eccentricities.
pero intento ser sincera y aceptar mis excentricidades.
- Right. - And I thought I would come say hi.
- Vale. - Y pensé en venir a saludar.
- Yeah, cool. - Where are your friends?
- Sí, guay. - ¿Y tus amigos?
This isn't a bad time, is it?
¿Es mal momento?
Yeah, you know, a little bit. I...
Sí, bueno, un poco....
- Oh, hi. - Oh, shoot.
- Ah, hola. - Caray.
- What's this? Are we speed dating? - No. Um...
- ¿Qué es? ¿Un bar de citas? - No.
This is Wesley.
Esta es Wesley.
- Wesley... we're old friends. - Yeah.
- Wesley, somos viejos amigos. - Sí.
- And, this is Ellen, my... - Blind date.
- Y esta es Ellen, mi... - Cita a ciegas.
- Yeah, that's pretty much... - It's weird to say out loud.
- Sí... - Es raro decirlo en voz alta.
- Yeah, someone set us up. - Oh, my gosh.
- Nos presentaron. - Madre mía.
That's so awesome.
Es increíble.
- Awesome. - She was like, "I know this nice guy."
Me dice: "Conozco a un chico".
And I was like, "Okay. I'm not doing anything
Y yo: "Vale. No hago nada
on a Wednesday." So...
los miércoles".
It's going okay. I'm talking too much. This feels weird. So...
Estoy hablando demasiado. Esto es raro...
- Do you... You should sit down. - No, no, no.
- ¡Siéntate! - No.
I should call my mom.
Voy a llamar a mi madre.
Her basement flooded yesterday, so I should check on her.
Su sótano se inundó ayer, así que debería ir a verla.
- Oh, no. - You guys, sit.
- No. - Quedaos aquí.
You haven't seen each other in a long time.
Hacía tiempo que no os veíais.
I hope her mom figures that out.
Ojalá se arregle lo de su madre.
Listen, I won't stay long. Um...
No puedo quedarme mucho rato.
I owe you a big thank-you.
Te debo una muy grande.
You recommended me for that Atwater job. Is that true?
Me recomendaste para un empleo. ¿Es cierto?
- This is true. - Thank you. I got it.
- Lo es. - Gracias. Me lo dieron.
I know. I know.
Lo sé.
Look, it's not a big deal. People come to me
Nada. La gente me pide...
asking for guidance counselor recommendations all the time.
que le recomiende orientadoras muy a menudo.
Oh, they do?
¿Sí?
Well, guidance counselors, drug dealers. Those two.
Orientadoras y traficantes.
Thanks for recommending me for the first.
Gracias por recomendarme.
- Yes, I did. Yeah. - I will try to not get fired.
- Sí. - Intentaré que no me despidan.
If you do, you can be a drug dealer.
Podrías ser traficante.
- Oh, yay. - Yeah.
- Ah, sí. - Sí.
- Oh, man. It's so good to see you. - Yeah, you too. Well...
- Me alegro de verte. - Sí, yo también. Bueno...
'cause you're very much on a date right now, but, um...
porque ahora mismo estás en una cita, pero...
I like you.
me gustas.
And I know I was hung up on Jared, but that's not my guy.
Estaba obsesionada con Jared, pero no era mi tipo.
And I feel like I'm myself around you.
Siento que a tu lado soy yo.
What if we just...
¿Y si...
What if we gave it a shot?
lo intentamos?
I like you too. I...
Tú también me gustas...
But?
¿Pero?
Wes, I don't think I'm... I don't think I'm there.
Wes, no creo que esté en ese punto.
You're literally on a date right now.
Estás en una cita ahora mismo.
This is casual.
Esto es casual.
What we had in Mexico was real.
Lo que teníamos en México era real.
You would be more than just a date.
Serías más que una cita.
You see, you deserve somebody that's gonna sweep you off your feet.
Te mereces a alguien que te haga levitar.
Am I able to be that person again?
¿Podré ser esa persona?
I wanna say that I am, but honestly...
Quiero decir que sí, pero...
Okay, I'm sorry I interrupted.
Siento haber interrumpido.
- Thanks, Sean. - Wes.
- Gracias, Sean. - Wes.
Hey.
Hola.
So...
Bueno...
basement's okay,
el sótano está bien,
but my brother's missing.
pero no está mi hermano.
I'm sorry. What?
Perdona. ¿Qué?
Like, on a date.
Si está en una cita...
Look...
Mira... no debía conocer a alguien tan pronto.
You know? I was... just getting my feet wet.
Quería ir poco a poco.
Oh, my God. You don't need to say that.
No hace falta que digas eso.
I... honestly, it's fine. I'm fine.
No pasa nada, estaré bien.
That's the thing, Wes. I'm not okay with just being fine.
Esa es la cuestión, Wes. No quiero estar solo bien.
I want more than that. I wanna be...
Quiero más que eso. Quiero...
crashed out on the side of the road,
tener un accidente
yelling at a bitch-ass goat...
y gritarle a una cabra...
with you.
contigo.
I wanna watch you dancing, you know?
Quiero verte bailar, ¿sabes?
Like you have nerve damage.
Aunque parezcan espasmos.
Wes, you are messy...
Wes, eres un desastre...
and complicated...
y complicada...
and so perfectly you.
y muy tú.
And I haven't felt like this in a long time,
Hace mucho que no me siento así
and I don't want it to end.
y no quiero que acabe.
Me neither, Sean.
Yo tampoco, Sean.
Wesley Darya...
Wesley Darya...
will you marry me?
¿Nos casamos?
- What?
- ¿Qué?
No, I don't wanna marry you, but I would like to date you.
No quiero casarme, pero me gustaría salir contigo.
Why do you think I'm here? I've been thinking about you ever...
¿Qué crees que hago aquí? Pienso en ti cada...
Shit.
Joder.
Hey.
Hola.
Yeah, no, the blind date's not going good.
No, la cita a ciegas no va bien.
'Cause he's kissing another girl on the street.
Porque está besando a otra chica.
I'm serious. Why does this keep happening to me?
¿Por qué me pasa siempre lo mismo?